When I first saw him, this dude
was standing in the middle of
the street on 15th Avenue with
foreign cars that, like, started
by remote control in the middle
of the street with Mike Tyson.
This is Mike Tyson, the
heavyweight champion of the
world, and he's in the middle of
the street of where you grew up
on 15th Avenue. This is one of
the things that you just never
forget.
In order to be in my presence,
he had to be making millions,
nigga. You gotta make millions
to hang out with me. It was no
other drug dealer like
Convertible Bird. You heard his
name every corner, everywhere.
He was that dude. You don't see
that. Like, he was the blue
print to the style of hip-hop
when it come from down south.
It might be 10 of Johns, but
it's only one convertible Bird.
This nigga be my daddy and he
riding through the ghetto in a
Mercedes-Benz, in a Rolls-Royce,
and a Chevy convertible. This
was my dream.