You could be nothing and become
something, you know what I'm
saying? He went and seen
Scarface and left the movie
theater and went and bought a
gray Porsche.
Out of the way, lady, we're
trying to fly here, all right?
He did his as a movie. I did
mine as facts. I got it just
like he got it. I got suitcases,
bags of money. I got
motherfuckers flying 2 and 3
keys of coke from this coast to
that coast to this coast. I got
all that.
You can sum up Scarface in two
words: bang bang, snort snort.
Bang bang is for gunfire, snort
snort is for cocaine. There's a
lot of both in Scarface.
And ain't just talking about it,
ask them white folks. It's
documented who I was. I built a
million-dollar house, I had
Rolls-Royces, every car you can
order. The world know who I am.
I'm here today telling this
story, man, telling this tale,
man.