Oh, Femi, I didn't mean it like
that. I mean, what I was trying
to say is— It's okay. Sex is not
everything. Just finish the
dishes. Just finish the dishes,
okay? I mean, people shouldn't—
should— should— should— gosh.
Please. Please. I don't have a
roommate. Should I. You go to
st. Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. Okay.
Yes, sir. Come on. Come on. Your
clothes. Wait, wait, let me show
you, let me show you, let me
show you, let me show you, let
me show you, let me show you.
Please open your eyes, Miss, for
me. You can do this. Can you
hear me? For me, you can do
this. I knew you could do it.
This is for me. Are you okay? Is
everything okay? Please talk to
me now. Sis, okay, please, can
you at least make a sound so I
know you're fine? Please, now,
sis. You know what, that's it,
I'm calling your husband.