He was there at
5. He was looking for
porn. Hey, man, come on in, man. Have a seat. Kick it with me for
a minute. Nah, not right now, bro. Got a lot of things to do.
Get you off. Corey!
Sit your ass down.
What's going on with you? You walk around here like somebody done stole your
lunch money. I can't get you to go nowhere. And when we do,
you ain't saying nothing. See you around the corner, you going all the way like
we in junior high. What's going on with you? Did I do something? Did I
say something? You know you could talk to me.
What's going on? Come on.
Nah, definitely not you.
It's messed up real bad.
Trying to get my head wrapped around it, you know?
Messed up how? It's messed up real
bad, bro. I gotta take care of this one this time, you know?
Say me? Some type of trouble or something, like with some loan
sharks or something? I mean, I ain't rich or anything like that, but I mean,
I could help you out with some money or whatever
you need. What? Stock money? It's nothing
illegal. Just serious women problems right now.
Shh. Hey,
don't tell me you're some weird essay bull.
Bro, no, no, no. Hell.
I wish I could tell you. I wish I could, bro. I just
gotta figure it out. I give up. All right.
You know, when you're ready to talk, you talk.
It's an open ear for you, man. Appreciate that. Okay. Look, man,
that's about it. All right. It's all right with you,
man. Oh, you got a hard life. Things ain't
the same since, you know. Yeah.
Sorry to hear that. I mean, I don't need to say
She forgave me, but I don't think she did.
Bro, you know you a dog.
Yeah, but for how long? You know, how long can this go on?
You know, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm saying, you know,
I feel bad 'cause it feels like I cheated, you know?
And I feel worse because I know, I know Nita wouldn't
do that to me. She's not like that.
Don't, don't, don't, don't feel that way. Don't ever
beat yourself up for these women, bro. 'Cause honestly,
we like to think they'll do one thing, but they always do the opposite.
You never know what a woman's capable of if they hurt. You hear me?