Hey,
what was that? Oh,
you heard that too? I think it was a bang from our
neighbor's compound. Oh, it was loud, isn't it?
Oh,
don't worry,
I'll get it.
Christian literature.
Okay. You know, I still
kind of find it hard to believe that you're now
a Jesus boy. I mean,
I keep reminiscing of them days when you
and I used to do some naughty— Boundaries,
Bianca. Boundaries.
No, I mean, I'm just saying I'm proud of you though.
Don't. You're not allowed to talk to me
about the past. That chapter is dead and buried. Are we
clear?
Hope you slept well, baby. Yes, I did. How are you? I'm good.
Where is Daddy? Where exactly did he travel to again?
Abuja. Oh, seems to be traveling a
lot, you know, now working and all. When is
he coming back? Is it— I, I don't
know, but why don't you call him? Oh, not happening.
No, baby,
I think you
should stop.