You should have seen the look on her face. Oh my
gosh, Aaron. Parker, I promise this
was not something I planned. All the more reason
why you shouldn't go through with it. Look,
all engagements aren't planned. When is the last time
that you have heard a guy go to the coffee shop, get to the counter,
the woman asks, "What would you like today?" and he says,
"Marriage, one day." And then she says, "Oh my God,
oh my God, oh my God, we're gonna get married!" Parker,
that was the worst analogy ever.
So, are you gonna be
my best man— woman?
You're really gonna marry her?
I don't want to break her heart. What about
mine? What? Nothing.
Parker, this is something she
has dreamed about her whole life. But what does that have to
do with you or me, for that matter? I need
you. Aaron,
you have been my best friend since elementary school.
And if you haven't noticed, I am a woman.
And I don't think she's gonna be that keen on me being around.
Parker, she doesn't have a choice. I mean, just like you always say,
we go back like old men' hairlines. Eric, this is
serious.
I can't say no.
And— And what?
I love her.
But are you in love with her?
I guess we have our whole lives to figure that out.
Well,
I've always been there for you,
and anything you need, I got you.
That's my girl. See? I knew you'd make me feel great
about this decision. Come on. Cheer up.
Yeah. I'm getting married.
Thank you. See, now I feel a lot better.
Mm-hmm. So,
how's your column? [SIGH] My
editor said it wasn't edgy enough. What was it?
Animal cruelty. Aren't you in the
entertainment section? Yes, but that's what it was about.
It was about getting entertainers to stop wearing fur.
That is so cruel. I mean, just think, how weird would it be if I
wore your skin? That would be creepy.
Exactly. See, Parker, I get your
point, but that's not entertaining.
You have to do something like give people suggestions or
something. Like what? I don't know.
Maybe do something like— have
people send you their love letters. And respond back to them like
a Q&A. That is so cliché. It's not cliché,
and it's perfect, and it's popular. I mean, people love that.
Everybody needs a therapist. Well, listen, I am not a therapist.
I am a writer. I don't know. I mean,
you do give me amazing advice.