Is all clear. Told you nobody was going to be here. They all gone
for their Christmas vacation.
Oh baby, this is so nice!
You can see the city from here, babe. I can't
believe you work here. You really came up in life. I told you I was
going to bring you somewhere nice. Wait till you see
the view from roof.
Let's save
that for dinner.
Save dinner
for later. Oh my God, what?
Is he dead? I can barely feel his
pulse. Dial 911.
Oh my God,
where am I? You're in the hospital, Mr. Henson. You've been
here for about 2 days now. 2 days?
What's going on? Let's check your chart,
okay? All right. It says here that you
may have fell at work and a janitor found you and did some chest compressions
and called the ambulance.
Ambulance? What's wrong with me?
How about we have the physician come in and talk to you about that,
okay? Doctor, would you— Ah!
Hold on. Pain everywhere in my body.
That's okay. I have something for that. Just try to relax,
okay? Just try to relax. I got something for that. Okay.
All right.
Just relax. I'm gonna get the doctor. I'll be right back.
Mr. Henson, my name is Dr.
Vero. How are you feeling right now?
Dizzy, but I'm okay.
I understand all of this may be a bit confusing to you.
A lot of this is confusing to me. I'm just trying to make some sense
of it. Give it to me straight, dog. What's going on?