Wow. Look, I'm sorry. I really don't mean for
things to be that harsh. It's just that you go back to Atlanta tomorrow
and I'm left here still continuing my life. I don't
think I should disrupt that.
My God, this lady. What? No, no, no, you good.
Keep talking. I'm listening. Go ahead. I've already said everything. Oh,
hold on one second. Let me answer this. Miss Rhymes?
Hi, Donald. Hey. So I
was able to work out a deal with Norman and Company. They offered
me numbers that, let's just say, I'm happy.
Very happy. However, there's no need for a middleman, and so
I'm relieving you of your duties. Wait, what do you mean you're relieving me?
We had an agreement. Donald, there's nothing else to talk
about. Yes, and my lawyer carefully viewed this
agreement. There's some things we aren't too
happy with. Wait, wait, hold on, hold on. I, I can fix
this. Let, let me fix this, okay? Donnie, you can't fix this.
You lived your life and now I'm living mine.
Frankly, Donald, there's nothing you can do. I have already
contacted Mr. Calhoun and informed him about my decision.
Excuse me,
I need to speak to my son.
Uh, he's all yours. Thank you.
Donnie, I need to talk to you, son. Oh, son?
Are you crazy?
I know you don't care for me much right now,
But this is important. I need to talk to you.
Back up. So you want to talk?
Now you want to talk, huh?
Like you father of the year now, right? Like you deserve
any of my time so I can indulge in what you want
or what you need. You've lost your goddamn
mind. I'm trying to talk to you.
I've been trying to talk to you.
Many times I've tried to talk to you,
but I couldn't muster up the courage to face you.
Does that make you happy? Does it make you feel good? That I was
embarrassed, I was ashamed, I was humiliated.
The guilt's been eating me up for years.