You want to
tell me what's going on?
Marcy Leanne Jewell Chandler.
Oh.
So I've been working with this big client.
Supposed to turn my little boutique agency
into a major player in the advertising world.
You know, but when Preston referred me to them,
I had no idea that they were embroiled in
this lawsuit. Well, maybe they weren't.
Knowing Preston, he probably saw the writing on the wall. But I had no
idea. Ooh. Had you
known, would you have taken them on anyway?
Marcy? Remember when you asked
me if there was a reason I hadn't been home?
Well, Mom, there are several reasons.
You know, everybody in this family has had success.
Everybody. I have cousins who have all these fancy
degrees and successful husbands and
perfect children. Everyone except for me.
I was always the flighty one.
The one who had to find her wings, find her way. And I
found my way. I did. I found
my way.
I finally found something that I'm really good at. When I found it,
I worked really hard to make sure that I could get better.
I was gonna show him. That's all that mattered to me,
was being the best advertising executive that
I could be. So when this client
fell into my lap, I just knew this was my
break. This was my chance. This was my opportunity
to prove to everybody that I could do it.
That I— I finally made it. So to
answer your question, I don't
know. I don't have an answer for
that, and, um, that scares me
a little bit. You know what's scarier, honey?
Deciding what to do now that you do know.