It's all itemized. If you guys look at line 29, you'll see
how much you made off your investments in the 770 accounts. If you guys
have any questions, email me. No, no, we good, we good. Thank you.
Thank you, first of all. Thank you for giving us the opportunity to invest
in your, you know, urban development program. Thanks, bro. Yeah. Yeah. That's cool.
But, uh, you good? Yeah,
I'm cool. You sure, man?
Okay, it's Carmen. Like, she's been tripping lately,
man. Like, the other night, she dropped my phone in a glass of water.
Mm. That ain't tripping, man. That's crazy. She's just been, like,
complaining and nagging, trying to bait me into arguments.
I don't know, guys. I'm just getting sick of it. Getting sick of it.
All right, look, if you want an outside opinion on
your marriage and you ready to— you know, listen and you can handle
it, let me know. So you Dr. Phil now?
No, no, I'm not Dr. Phil. I'm just saying, look,
honestly, no disrespect, right? When we go out as couples,
Jasmine, you know, she all on my lap. Samira, she all on his shoulder.
You know, you and Carmen, you on one side of the room,
she on the other. For real, it's like the other night, like game night.
Y'all look like y'all was about to have a boxing match or something. No.
Yeah, no. I'm telling you. Look, look, look, whatever, man. Look, that's your wife,
right? All she wants is affection.
That's it. How you think she feels she see us with our wives
and you over there in the corner on your phone? On that phone, man.
OK, now you just making stuff up. I'm making it up?
Oh, I'm trying to holler at you from a place of love, right?
When last time you tapped that? Dude, that's disrespectful, man.
What? D, you ain't got no chill. So disrespectful. What? What did you do?
Why y'all up in the man's bedroom? I'm just saying, look, I remember her.
Like walking around, right? She looked like she was full of life. She had a
glow. She had this light about her. Now she got a sad face all the
time, like she, you know, mean-mugging us and stuff. Look, enough about my wife,
all right? Sorry I even brought it up. Look, I'm just saying, that's your wife,
right? She's a woman. She needs attention. You know, she's like a little flower.
You got to water it, show it attention, love and affection. She wants
that from her husband. Look, I'm telling you, you better do that, 'cause there's a
lot of thirsty dudes out there in the streets. They can see her coming from
100 miles away. Pssh, whatever, man. It's whatever?