I think. But,
yo, I'll give up everything for her and that baby. No,
you are, man. You better not be playing with me. You think it's mine?
Of course it's yours, man.
Whoa. Yeah.
I'm having a baby.
Jihad. This whole time I've been pushing Carmen away,
this part of me felt guilty that I couldn't give her the family that she
always wanted. Put my business
first, trying to become this ultimate entrepreneur.
This whole time, I've been neglecting my baby,
taking her for granted.
I was selfish. Not anymore.
There you go. Okay. You hear me? Cause I'm ready to be a father,
man. But I'm gonna start by being a better husband.
That's what I want to hear. You better be. Give me something. Give me some.
Thank you, brother. And that's the night
it happened. Why I missed dinner. Mm.
I'm so sorry.
For what? It's for the best. I mean,
congratulations. What's with the
change of heart? Cause you love him. I can't compete with that.
Well, I got a better chance of swimming backstroking across
the Pacific Ocean before I break a woman who purely loves her man.
You know, I was. I was once married to
a woman quite like you. You were once married? August was
married. Really? Yes. He was 18 years old,
fresh out of high school. I was working on my real estate business,
and she.
She signed up for the military and eventually got
sent off to war.
She. She calls
me one day and hears this female's voice
in the background. Uh,
It's the first time we ever got off the phone without saying we love each.
Two days later, I get a call that my
wife. My wife was
killed.
But, you know, I mean,
the female's voice she heard was my roommate's
girlfriend's voice. And, you know, I was having problems with the bills and took a
roommate and had too much pride to tell my wife.
I'm really sorry to hear that. Yeah,
well, my motto now is,
if you love them, tell them.
Because believe me when I tell you, a person is here today and they're gone
tomorrow. Carmen,
if you love your husband, tell your husband.
Thank you, Fran. You're welcome.
Now, that bedroom back there.
Did you. Shut up. Stop it. You can't blame it for
trying. I can, but I won't. Oh, no.
Listen, I'm sure you'll figure it out,
but I better be going. I got a meeting in
about an hour. Okay. Thank you. Okay,
we'll talk later.