Yeah, Mom. Yeah, no, everything's. Everything's great. She's been really, really busy.
Yeah.
How's Carmen?
Carmen is Carmen.
Hey, Mom. When dad was alive,
how did you guys make your marriage work?
Cause I want to work. Silence is
loudness. The words you
don't speak speak volume.
If the caged bird don't sing, then what's its use
to me? It's like a chef without a recipe.
No food for thought, I hope. There it is.
Saving you. Saving me from a broken dear.
Carmen, would you please be my girlfriend?
Yes. Maybe.
No.
P.S. please say yes.
What are you doing?
We're in fourth grade.
Carmen. I know you're pregnant.
I came here to fight for you.
You're going back home with me if I have to burn this house down.
Baby, I hear you. I see
you. I'm so sorry for all
my selfish crap, pushing you away.
I always felt that I couldn't give you the family that
you deserve. The family we always wanted.
Carmen,
I don't. Okay, okay.
Remember six years ago when we went to the doctors and he
said it would be like one in a billion chance that
you would be able to conceive? Carmen, the fact that you are pregnant
is a sign. It's a sign,
baby. And I'm willing to do whatever it takes to
win you back.
This is me and you. It's always been me and you,
Carmen. Carmen Elizabeth, right?
I love you. And I always have.
Since the fourth grade.
I don't wanna lose you. I don't
wanna lose you. I love you.
Omar, right?
I love you so much. And then some
whole bunch nice, you know?
But I love her even more. You know what?
What? I love her more too.
Let's have another. I'm start.