Yo. Hey, what's up, man? What's up, man? All right?
Yeah, I'm good. Samira asked me to bring you a plate, man. We know
you over here starving to death. Man, make sure you tell her I said thanks.
No doubt. You know I had to put your wife out yesterday, right? Yeah,
she told me that. They're only looking out for you guys,
you know? Yeah, but it's over
between me and Carmen. Yeah. I don't understand that. Oh,
I mean, you guys are meant for each other. She's divorcing
me, Jahad. Don't you understand? She just did that to get some attention.
Okay, now you sound like your wife. You don't give someone divorce papers
for attention. She's a woman. Do they ever really need an excuse
to do anything?
By the way, Carmen's pregnant.
I will dump that whole plate of food on your head. She's pregnant, though.
That's impossible. I'm sterile. I've been that way for
years. What are you talking about? Oh, I guess those sperm counts have risen from
the dead, huh?
Carmen's what?
Are you serious? Yeah.
Okay, if Carmen's pregnant, it's probably because she was messing around. Oh, come on.
Nah, man, she has been talking to this— this Boris Kodjoe
real estate-looking cat. Really? Now you're talking crazy.
You know Carmen better than anyone, dog, and she isn't out
there like that, and you know it.
No, no, no, no. Maybe she's doing this to keep me from going to Europe.
Come on, dog. She loves you.
Besides, Samira and Jasmine were there with her when she took the test.
4 times. All positive.
We've been
trying to have children for years.
But now we're going to the divorce court. So what does this all mean?
His job?
Wait a minute.