Hey baby, it's okay. You scared
me, you scared me, you scared me. Don't you
ever do that again, okay?
Sis, don't ever do that.
Whatever it is, you talk to me,
okay? We're partners in this. I don't care what
you're feeling. You come to Mommy and you tell Ah,
I am your mom. Whatever he's
saying, he doesn't mean it. Tell her.
Yes.
Just give me the baby. I was so scared.
I love baby. I love you
too. Hey,
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said too
much. Yes, you should learn how to keep your big mouth shut.
I deserve that, but I'm
sincerely sorry. I'll never do anything to hurt you or our
child. Our child?
Just a few minutes ago you were telling me how she's not
my child. I'm sorry, Catherine.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
And everything goes back
to normal.
So you think you just say
I'm sorry and that's it? Oh,
I'm sorry I slept with my secretary.
I'm sorry she's pregnant for me.
So you really think I like your I'm
sorrys? I don't. So why don't you wrap
them up? And keep it for her when
you cheat with the next secretary. Please, I'm not getting
married to her. All I wanted was the child.
Do you hear yourself? I almost feel sorry for her.
Where are you going? To the guest room.
He's sleeping in the guest room. Because that's where
guests sleep. I'm obviously a guest here
now. In fact, I'm prepping the house for your new wife
and child. Oh, you know, expecting mothers,
they need space. My days are numbered here. Stop it,
Catherine. I'm not expecting any wife or
child, and you're not sleeping in the guest room. Who is going
to stop me? You? Please give
me a reason.