We began this
never-ending argument.
Days, you know how it goes. I blame
you, you blame me. No one wants to give in to the other.
Has war ever made peace? I thought we loved
each other. If we don't fight for something much
greater, we may wake up 20 years
later looking back,
let's subtract all the time we place.
We attack and react. We don't want
to change. If the fight don't kill us,
then our pride just may.
And I can't carry this one more day. It ain't
worth the way. It ain't
worth the way.
It ain't worth the way. You're my
sister. You're my The only one who truly
sees who I am. Girl,
you know me and how I get.
And I know you far too well to ever let
it get to the point where— I blame you, you blame me.
No one wants to give in to the other.
No one has ever made peace. I thought we loved
each other. You make your list of amends? Yeah, yeah, I got them.
Got them right here. Here you are.
No, please read aloud.
Number 1, to see my daughter and get her to talk to me again.
How long has it been now?
8 years. Number 2,
get my gig back at the club. Playing piano down at Drake's, right?
Yeah. Number 3, uh,
get my family to forgive me.
Which you doing first? My daughter.
What are you gonna do?
I got a plan.