This is where you want to be.
A place of precision and glamour.
I mean, look at this space. It's a piece with its own fashion
statement. A statement
of flawless style, poise,
very adventurous. So now,
ladies and gentlemen, if one ordinary picture is
worth a thousand words, then a piece like this
is worth every penny in your wallet. For every
penny in my wallet. I want the picture of a naked woman.
Well, you don't look like a man who has a problem getting women naked.
Why settle for a painting, darling? Paintings don't break your
heart. Well, unfortunately, we're not in a season for erotic here.
Make you follow
me.
The Salon Room. Kallinikos.
Untitled portrait. Isn't it beautiful? I guess.
I don't know anything about paintings. So why come here?
Because I'm one of the two kinds of people that come to an art gallery.
The first: rich, bored women that have more money than they
know what to do with. Hey.
Hey. And the second?
Young men looking for rich, bored women to fill
their wallets.
Amazing. So good.
This is
for you.
Chima Eze. Hopewell. Tari Hopewell.
Your passion for naked women, I hope it
translates to a satisfying experience for the both of us.