Well, good morning, honey.
I am almost done with breakfast. Oh, good morning. Good morning.
You look amazing. Thank you. And it smells fantastic
in here. That's because I only made your favorites.
Thank you. Oh, figured I'd spoil
you a little bit before the day got started. Mm-hmm. Especially after last night.
Well, you've outdone yourself as usual.
So babe, what's on your agenda for today? Well, I've got a
few in-person client meetings talking about the
server usage, so that may result in a long
day. It's no problem. I mean, I'll just handle everything here.
I'm gonna start by pulling the weeds out back, and then after that,
I'm finally gonna tackle the garage. We gotta make space for
our winter clothes anyway. I know it's a long list, but oh,
you know how much I love a clean garage. Yeah, you love
a clean garage just as much as you love a well-organized closet. Guilty as
charged.
Okay, I gotta go.
You don't. I do. I've gotta get to work. I gotta get to the office.
Why can't you stay? Come here.
I'll be here. Mm-hmm. Good luck on your meetings today,
but please be safe driving. I will. Okay. I will. All right,
I love you. Love you too.
All right, you better get out of here before you get something started. Oh,
is that a threat? Babe, don't play with me. What you working with?
Why you playing? Why you playing? You're already in love. Okay, I gotta
go. I gotta go. I'm gonna be late. All right, sorry. I love you.
I love you too.