When I first saw him, this dude was standing in the middle of the street
on 15th Avenue with foreign cars that like,
started by remote control in the middle of the street with Mike Tyson. This is
Mike Tyson, the heavyweight champion of the world. And he's in the middle of the
street of where you grew up on 15th Avenue. This is one of the things
that you just never forget. In order to be in my presence, he had to
be making millions. Nigga had to make millions to hang out with me.
It was no other drug dealer like Convertible Bird.
You heard his name every corner, everywhere. He was that dude.
You don't see that like he was the blue print to the style of
hip hop. When it come from down south. It might be 10 of John's
but it's only one convertible bird. This could be my daddy and he riding through
the ghetto in a Mercedes Benz and a Roll Royce and
a and a Chevy convertible this was my smooth.