Me. Sade in
all her glory. And how long have you been standing there?
Well, long enough to fantasize how to get a husband
like you. How sweet. Anyway,
I gotta go. Take care of your sister. If she gives you any trouble,
just call me, okay? Wow. All right. Boo.
Aw. Jealous much?
Sh.
Come here. A Smuggling.
How are you? H so
sorry. When did you come in? Early this morning. How do you say
not to disturb you? He was just nosing. I know.
Man. That stupid anxiety tab.
Why do you still take them? I don't have a choice.
Jolfa rice, chicken,
fruits. Where did you meet this amazing man again?
I was raped and shot. And he was a
doctor on duty. Are you really sure you want
to go down that road? I didn't think so either.
Just me. Jo. What have you been up to,
girl? The usual. You know.
I have plenty. Jeez. For you. You did what? Broke up
with him. Why? So I learned. Because this is the third guy this
year, dummy. Yeah, but sis, you know me. A broken relationship
is better than a broken marriage. That line again?
Yes, that line again. But you know me. I won't settle
for less. What's this crime? Sex.
The guy wants to have sex in the morning, in the afternoon,
all the time. I may be everything,
but a dog is not on the list. No.
I thought that's what this generation is all about. Sex, sex, sex,
sex. They can't get enough of sex. My sentiments exactly.
Well, let's talk about you. I mean, you've been having sex for over
four years now. What has he done for you?