It's all clear. Told me nobody's gonna be here.
They all going for their Christmas vacation.
Oh, baby, this is so nice.
You can see the city from here.
Babe. I can't believe
you work here. You really came up in life. I told you I was gonna
bring you someone nice. Where did you see the view roof?
Is he dead? I could barely
feel his pause down 91 1. Oh, my God.
Where am I? You're in the hospital, Mr. Henson. You've been
here for about two days now. Two days? What's going
on? Let's check your chart. Okay.
All right, it says here that you may have fell at work.
And the janitor found you and did some chest compressions and called
the ambulance. The ambulance? What's wrong
with me? How about we have the physician
come in and talk to you about that, okay?
Doctor, would you hold on?
Pain everywhere in my body. That's okay. I have something for that.
Just try to relax, okay? Just try to relax. I got something for that.
Okay? All right.
Just relax. Get the doctor. I'll be right back.
Mr. Henson, my name is Dr. Vero.
How are you feeling right now?
Dizzy. I'm okay.
I understand all of this may be a bit confusing to you.
A lot of this is confusing to me. I'm just trying to make some sense
of it. Give it to me straight, dog. What's going on?