Mr. Henson, you have a rare autoimmune disorder called
Koodpasture syndrome. This disorder actively
attacks the kidneys. We've given you medication to
stabilize your pain and symptoms. However, the disease is growing rapidly.
Being that it is a chronic disorder, you may have had
it for some time. Now. Hold on. Wait a minute, Doc. What?
What are you trying to tell me? Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Why? Is it a pastor here? No, look, Doc,
I'm just a little dehydrated, overworked, that's all.
I'm okay, Doc. Mr. Henson,
most people have a life expectancy of five to ten years on
dialysis. Okay. Well, unfortunately for you, you are at
the end stages of liver failure, which means dialysis
wouldn't be much help.
And without a transplant,
The prognosis is three weeks. Three weeks?
The pastor is here. If you would like to talk this through with the man
of faith. I don't need to talk nothing out with a man of faith.
You got the wrong guy. That's the wrong patient. All right, listen, I'm okay,
Doc. I know it's difficult to accept,
but with your results and my professional
evaluation,
I think it would be best for you to call your family and be with
them for the holidays.
I am going to write you a prescription that's
going to take care of the pain. No heavy lifting and keep driving to a
minimum, please.
Here's my card. If you have any questions or concerns.
I got a lot of questions. I got a lot of concerns.
What about my job? What about my career?
Who's gonna take care of that?