Now, look, y' all gonna stay with your mama Rose for a while.
So y' all be good to her. When are you coming back to us?
Why can't we go with you? Because you can.
Ain't no place for little boys. All right,
Look, I'm coming back.
Don't look at me like that. I'm. I am. I'm coming back. I'll come back
with y' all when things get right, okay?
But for now, I need you to go.
Don't look at me like that. Go.
Gone now.
Go be with family for your holidays. You should be around
loved one during this tentative time.
Hi, Donald. It's Cheyenne. I would like to meet this afternoon
for lunch. There's a few matters we need to discuss.
1:00 clock at my place. I'll see you there.
These people don't know what they talking about.