You probably don't want to hear, but Normandy and company, they do have the advantage.
That's not what I wanted to hear. Well, as of now,
your job right now is to force them to amend this contract.
That's renegotiation of high dividends, percentages,
limiting their rights. The only way they'll go for that is if
they think that's their better option. So what do you propose?
Your attorney has to find some kind of arguable loophole in the contract.
Whether he use it or not, that's up to him. But the agenda
is to make Normandy Co. Believe that you can win this.
Now. Also, you got a high class publishing company behind you
that's willing to pay legal fees at your leisure.
That double sided disadvantage will force them into litigation.
Once we go to litigation, you have the upper hand because you
have the higher percentage. Hmm.
I knew that I liked you. I knew
there was a reason I liked you. Ah.
Are you okay? Do you need some water?
I'm fine. Are you sure? I'm fine,
I'm fine, I'm fine. Okay, good. Carry on.
All right, good. If you can send
me a list of publications, that would be great. My lawyer will take
care of all the clauses. Okay. I Gotta be honest, Ms.
Rhymes. Everything's closed up for the holidays. Nobody's answering the
phone. Hmm. It is that time of
season. It is. I don't believe in holidays.
I work all holidays. Me either, Ms. Rhimes.
Oh. You're on my team for a reason.
We don't get distracted by holidays, right? Absolutely not. Okay,
good. So I should get a list of contingents by the end of the
week. Okay. And it was good seeing you. Oh, always good to see you,
Ms. Rimes. Thank you. You got it. All right. Take care.