Hello, Donald. Can you meet me in my office?
Absolutely, Mr. Calhoun.
Mr. Calhoun. How's it going, man? It's going good. Thanks for coming down.
Absolutely. How's it going? It's going good right
now. Sending out some emails and a list of prospects for Ms. Rhymes as
we speak. I've been getting some notifications that you've been having some fading
spells and you've been in the hospital. I'm fine. I just need some sleep,
that's all. And apparently a lot of water. I know what it's like
being a young go getter. Aggressive, ambitious,
resilient. I remember those days myself.
But you got to take care of yourself. I know you're a hard worker.
Yeah, I know you're a hard worker. But you got to keep at it.
And I value you so much that
you've got to take care of yourself. I promise I will, Mr. Calhoun.
Tell you what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna give you Christmas Eve, and I'm gonna
give you Christmas Day off. Well, wait a minute. You told me I had to.
I had to. I had to work. No, take the time. Take the time.
Get the rest. Okay?
All right. And I know you will. I know you will, because I'm
going to cancel your access privileges until next
Monday. Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.