Yeah, man. No, after you. After you,
man. Listen, man, I remember, man. You going in
Mama Rose corn tub just to get a po Boy. No, no, no. That was
you taking the quarters out there. Listen, listen, I want the only one. You got
your hand stuck in there a couple of times, too. Taking it to my grave.
Yeah. Okay, okay. Let me get two shrimp po boys,
two strawberry daiquiris. Make mine small because I.
I gotta drive. I gotta drive. Oh, no, I got you. I got this black
car. But we only accept cash, sir. Ah, so I got
it. I got it, cuz. Kind of place that don't take cars.
I mean, I'm sure that there's an ATM around here,
big time. It's 20, 23, man. Come on.
Yeah, it ain't that serious. I. I got us. I got us.
I got us.
So what's up with Darius, man? Oh, D, man,
D doing real good. Ever since he got out of county.
Got himself straight. Got a real good construction job.
Real good. Okay. Where you stand at?
He at Mama Rose. But, but, but it's by choice,
though. Cause he making good bread to get his own spot. Yeah.
Why does he want to stay at Mama Rose House, man? I mean,
everybody got their views on this place, man. Maybe he see the beauty, but maybe
something different for you. Yeah. Oh, thanks, Grace. You're welcome. Thank you.
Who's your friend? My friend? This is my cousin Donnie.