Hey, man. So please tell me about Aaliyah. See, I knew that's what you was
talking about all this time. Thank you, Slick, man, but no, man, she's good,
man. She actually got a man now. Really? And he. He owns a fish spot
down here. Okay, but listen, man, Darius be joking on all
the time, man. He calls old boy Aquaman.
Oh, man, that's so crazy.
It's good to see you, little bro. Man, good to see you, too. Need to
get that weight up, though.
Let me look at you. I tell you. My, oh, my, you starting to look
more and more like Mike.
No, I don't look like him. And I go by Donald now.
Oh, okay. Okay. Well, are you hungry? I'm about to start
cooking. You want to eat now or. I'm okay, Auntie. We stopped by and got
Po boys on the way. Now, Scooter, why would you do something like that?
I told you that I was going to cook. It's okay, Auntie Jean. I.
I ate already, and then I'm a little tired, too. Oh, this is a bit
much for me. Yeah. So I'm going to lay it down.
Okay. Thank you. Well, you know where your old room is, and you got fresh
covers on the bed. All right? Goodness to you. Absolutely.
What do you mean it's a bit much? This is his house. What do you
mean by that? Don't take it personal, Auntie.
You know how that big city is. It changes people. Make them
forget who they are and where they come from.
I'm sure he'll come around. Yeah, I'm sure he will.
You know what that mean, though, right? Know what?
More food for me. Boy, you crazy. Just make
sure to save some for your brother. Yes, all right. I do my best.