Well, you should get like me, and maybe your pockets will change.
You know something? I think being out
in Atlanta done made you cocky. Let's see how far
they get you down here.
Darius. Darius, tell your cousin Donnie about your new job.
I mean, you know, it's just a little construction job, that's all.
But. But no. Remember you told me that they were looking at you for the
supervising position? Tell them. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, they did. Well, tell them that. Tell them that. Now. You know,
Donnie ain't trying to hear nothing like that.
Yes, I am. Tell me about your little construction
job. Well, all right.
I got a construction job.
And it's downtown, where they're expanding and building a lot of
new restaurants and hotels, and it's a great opportunity for us.
The pay is real good, too. And I
heard that they was. You know, they was looking for me to fill the supervisor
position. You heard? They was looking for a superpower.
Okay. Good for you. Good for you.
You see, I just won't like to tell you nothing.
Come on, man. Play cards. Play your cards. Play cards, man.
Hey. Hey, Mike.
I told you not to come today. He needs more time,
Rose. He's my son. I just want to see my son, that's all. I just
want to see him. Can I do that?
Hey, Donnie. What's up, baby? What's up? Come on, now. Just. What the hell you
doing here, Mike? Wait. Donnie, Donnie, Donnie.
He started coming back around a few years ago. He said he wanted to make
things right between us. Oh, no. He wanted to make things right between you.
You ain't got a damn thing to say to me.
Don't be like that, Donnie. Come on. I can't believe
you got the nerve to stand your ass in front of me
right now.
Donnie, I just want to see my son,
all right? And don't look at your mama. Rose. It was
me. She told me not to, okay? It was me.
She did. She told me not to, but I. I just want to see my
son, man. Can I see my son? That's all I want. I just want to
see my son. Please. You have been dead
to me for 15 years, and it is impossible
to bring the dead back to life. Can you
understand that?