Hello. Donald here. Donald. Good news? No, great news.
We found three clauses in the contract. So, how things
looking on your end? Things looking good. That's what I like to hear.
Okay, we'll be on standby all day tomorrow, okay?
Whoa. Tomorrow's Christmas. And since when did
you care? Anywho, I'll talk to you later,
okay? All right, bye. When I grow up, I'm gonna have my
own comic store here on the West Bay. I'm not just gonna sell comics.
I'm gonna sell all kinds of cool books. The books that get people going,
you know? That sounds boring. I think it's a good idea. And maybe
you'll have so much money that you can help people write their own books and
sell them in your store. Help people write and sell their books.
I like that. I.
I don't want to hear nothing you gotta say. Darius, that's not my father.
This ain't about Mike.
It's about Mama Rose.
You know, she really do wear her heart on her sleeve when it comes to
Maybe you ain't even noticed, and you
probably never will. But she loves you.
She loves you. We all love you.
I never said y' all didn't. But I was ambushed in there.
Ambush? You act like we invited him. You knew he was coming.
But ain't nobody telling me nothing.
You right. And that's my bad.
My fault.
I should have told you. We've been in contact. Yeah, you should have told me,
all right.
You right, Don. I should
have told you. I can't change