So, what's up?
You gonna come inside or what?
Hey, I'll meet you out there, bro. I'm gonna go change real quick.
Bonfire for Papa Noel. Boy, I ain't seen one of these in a long
time, man. My favorite part of Christmas. It ain't Christmas
yet. I know that. This is my favorite Christmas thing to do. Let me get
over here in the
house. Hey. Hey. How you doing?
I'm good. How are you? I'm good. Hey, get you and Leon
a bowl of gumbo. Yes, ma', am. I sure am. Hey, Mama Rose. Y' all
going over there by the bonfire. I got this. Y' all take. I got.
Take your bowls with you. You sure? I'm positive. Going on? Hey, what up,
fish man? My name's Leon,
man. Everybody over here call you the fish man. Who calls me
Daddy. Hey. Hey. How you doing?
Pretty good. Good, good. So are you doing it or am I?
I am. I'm. I'm doing it. Tell you what, I'm going hook you up right
now. There you go.
All right. For you and the fish man. You guys
have got to stop calling him that. It's just jokes.
I'm just playing. I'm joking. All right, does anybody
know why we light bonfires all through the week up
to Christmas Eve? Anybody? Any?
Oh, you, sir. We like bonfires
so Papa Noel can find its way to our houses to deliver presents.
Good job, Zion. Good job.
Good job. Done it.
Donnie, what's wrong? Are you okay?
I'm fine. Are you sure? I'm fine.
I'm fine. I'm just tired. If something was wrong, you would tell me, right?
Of course. I just need to lay down, that's all. All right. Enjoy your food.
Leo.