You got some nerve disrespecting me in here like this.
Disrespecting you? You just came over here and smacked
me in front of everybody. Well, you over here talking when you told me you
were gonna be at home. I'm not making a big deal out of it.
I just came to get something to eat,
man. He don't deserve my man. That dude be treating us so wrong,
bro. What's so wrong? Wasting our time, man.
He ain't nothing tripping.
You know what, guys? I think it's best if I ask him. Oh,
man, you ain't got to go nowhere. Don't forget him. Yeah, let him
go. Go home and soak in his own misery. He'll realize what he got lit
on. Yeah. Besides, chasing out the him ain't
gonna do nothing but boost his already inflated ego, so you might as
well stay. Yeah. And hey,
next round's on dying. Wait, hold on. I don't even drink,
man. Come on, bro. Black car dying. Let's go, man. Exactly. Let's go, cuzzo.
I really did enjoy this.
You always want me pants you big time.
Whatever. Did you see Donnie?
Are you happy?
I guess so. I mean, like, really happy.
How do you feel? Do you feel like you made the right decision to leave
all this behind? You know what? At first I thought I did.
But now that I'm back home, it feels like I'm.
Like I've been running for myself. What is that supposed to
mean? I mean, I think only if I
would have just gave this place a chance, then everything would have been okay.
Can I ask you a question? Sure.
What in the world do you see in Leon? Oh,
my God. Please tell me. Listen,
I know how it looks, but it's really not that bad.
We have more good times than bad ones. Yeah.
Can I tell you something? Yes,
of course. When you left town
for good, it really hurt me, you know?
We had so many plans, so many ideas, and it's like all
my dreams and ideas, they just left with you. And shortly
after that, my parents divorced and things just got
really, really tough. I could have really used a friend.
You know what I'm sorry about.