Who wants to say grace?
Who? I'll do it.
Okay. Go ahead.
God, I know it's been
a while. Not only since I've spoken to you,
but since we've been together like this as
a family. Sometimes we
don't realize the love we need from family. And so often we
take it for granted. But that's
why I'm praying to you today. Because my
heart is filled with so much joy. And I want
to personally thank you. I want to thank you for this food.
I want to thank you for this family.
And most of all, I want to thank you for Mama Rose.
Thank you for covering and protecting her.
In your name I pray. Amen.
Amen. That was beautiful. Good job.
Awesome. Let's eat.
Hey, sweetie. How you doing? Come on. I'm sorry I'm late.
Take a seat. No, you right on time.
Look at Mama Rose. She thinks he's so sleep.
Oh, yeah. You know she been playing matchmaker. I'm keeping all of what she
doing. She ain't sleep.