So you want my sympathy? Is that what this is?
Because you ain't gonna get the satisfaction when
you left us on Mama Rose doorstep and
looked me in my eyes and lied to me. Hold on. Let me quote this
right, because I don't want to get Mike wrong. You said imma
be back when everything is all right. Hey, Mike.
Is everything all right? Or did it get more complicated?
You got one more time to call me Mike. You know
that's not fair. Fair? You better get your hand out of my fair.
You want to talk about fair? My life ain't fair.
I despise this place because of what it
remind me of. Hand me downs, po Christmases,
Mama Rosa working her ass off the
love of my life. I done lost her. Cause every time
I think about this place, I think about you abandoning me.
That's enough, Donnie.
Really, Darius? Now tell
me something. You ain't mad at him a little bit? Just a little bit
when you look at him, Tell me what you see.
Cause I'm gonna tell you what I see.
I see disgust in everything a father shouldn't
be. You don't
think I was angry?
I was mad every single day.
And that anger. That anger made me do
hurtful things. Things that I went to prison for.
All because I ain't have nothing but hatred in my heart.