And I thought by coming back here,
there some odd reason that the love of
my family was just gonna heal me.
Silly, right? To think that my
family, the love that y' all had for me was gonna make me okay.
All they did was was rip a the band aid
off a old wound. But guess what?
Thank you. Thank all y'. All.
Merry damn Christmas. Donnie.
Donnie. Donnie. Donnie. Donnie. No, no, no,
no, no. Let him go. School. There he is.
He should not be alone right now.
Donnie. Donnie. That's what he wants.
All right. We heard him loud and clear.
Wow. That was. Intense. Yet oddly
interesting. Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Who's this? Cheyenne rhymes.
Is the fight over?
Where have you been, Daddy? We've been looking for you.
He's not coming back, is he? Why? Don't he love
us? Oh, Dottie, he loves you. He does.
He just got his own demons he's dealing with. It's been hard for him since
your mama passed,