Has anyone reached him yet? No, it keeps going straight to
voicemail. I mean, why not just let
him be? I mean, he said he wants to be left alone. Why not just
respect his wishes? Something just don't feel right.
I'm telling you. Just keep trying to call him Gene. All right? Okay.
All right.
Hello, Donald. I hope you're enjoying your Christmas vacation.
Mr. Calhoun. Let's just say I'm ready to get my butt
back. Well, before you get all hasty, there is something I wanted to discuss.
Let me guess. Ms. Cheyenne Rhymes?
Bingo. How on earth did you let that slip through your hands?
Wait, what do you mean? She. She chose to go with Norman
and Company. Donald, she was our biggest client. You really let us down.
And I thought since you two shared the same meager upbringing,
that you could speak her language and we'd have this one in the bag.
Nah. Sorry to do this to you, Donald. No, no,
no, listen. She's just trying to cut us out, man.
Look, and I didn't even write the contract as a matter. I did
everything you told me to do, Mr. Calhoun. I'm sorry,
Donald. You may return on Monday to pick up your belongings.
HR is sending a termination letter to your company email.
Mr. Calhoun, please listen to me. I've dedicated my
life to this company. Please don't do this to me. Your efforts don't
go unnoticed. I will personally provide a reference to you for your next job.
But when an agency like ours loses a client like she, Ann Rimes,
there are consequences. And, Donald, you are that consequence.
Hello? Mr. Calhoun, listen to me. Just. Just listen to me.
Hello, Mr.