Take my hands.
I'm really sorry Christmas didn't turn out how you wanted that.
It's all good. Mardi Gras is just a
good time to celebrate Christmas anyway.
Never thought my life would be like this. Like what?
I mean, good. Everything that's happening
is like. It's meant to be, you know? That's what healing
feels like. Yeah. You know, it's the other side that everyone wants to get to,
but they don't know how to. You know,
laying up in that hospital, I just. I realized what family meant.
You know, it was the reason why I was alive. You know,
it just made me understand what the true meaning of family was, you know?
So, Auntie Jean,
Uncle Russ, and of course,
you. Me? Yeah.
I made the mistake of losing you before. I'm not
losing you again. I'm staying my butt right here, babe.
Okay. So what about your job? Forget that
job. They don't care about me, and I damn sure don't care about them.
As a matter of fact, I'm gonna start my agency. And I'm My bookstore.
I'm gonna start my bookstore up. Are you scared? I'm serious. I'm serious.
Baby know you and Leon still together,
and y' all look happy and all that, but you cannot deny the fact that
we have chemistry. Well,
after the fight the other day, I realized how toxic and angry
y' all can be. And looking at how short life is,
I don't want to spend the rest of my that way. So I
ended it. Like, end.
Wow. Okay. Don't look so excited.
I'm not.
But you see what you're doing right now? I just love that.
I love to see you smile, Leah. That's all.
I see what you're doing. What I'm doing?
I'm innocent. For me to know innocent.