Thank you, Lord. Thank you for helping us find
our way. Man, who would have thought?
This has been one of the best holiday seasons ever. That changed
my life, you know, for the better. You know,
that's loving, family, blessings and forgiveness.
This is what I've been missing all along.
Thank you all for coming out to my official bookstore opening.
Now I gotta do this right. Hold on.
I'd like to introduce our first author and client to the Henson Agency,
Ford Thompson. Congratulations.
Thank you all for coming out.
O.
It's Christmas every day? When I'm with you?
Just like a candle in flame,
my love? It burns for you every
day? Like the star on the tree?
You shine better when we? When we're
together? Baby, let it snow?
Cause I wanna cuddle and rub you?
Make love to you all Christmas alone?
It's like mistletoes everywhere we go? Cause all
I wanna do Is kiss on your girl? Yeah,
I'm with you? It's Christmas every
day? Don't need no jingle bell?
I just need you right, baby? It's Christmas
every day? Monday through Sunday?
All through the year? When I'm with you?
It's Christmas every day?
Don't need no jingle bell?
People outside carol and fill with the
joy.