Yeah. Come on. It's lovely when the boys play right together
with you.
I want to see where this goes. Donnie, right? I also want to take
this slow. Maybe we can take it as slow as you want to. I know
I got a lot of making up for you. 10 years left.
You know, wise man once
told me that if you love her, you give
her something pretty. He also said that
if you love her and she have your babies,
that you put some respect on her name.
Yo, chill. I'm trying to be. Trying to be serious.
Yana Hill. We've been together for five
years, and you
don't put up with a lot of my nonsense for your name
not to be Mrs. Williams.
Young hell,
Will you marry me?
I seen Scope.
Hey, you know you got to be my best man, right? Come on, man.
It be my pet. You know that.
I hope. I hope this ain't going a
little too fast, but.
That ain't moving too fast,