I don't guess you're gonna help with the bags. Can you grab those? Do you
mind? Ma.
Hi, hon.
What's going on?
Oh, good to see you. Oh,
she looks beautiful as ever, baby.
So good. Mom, what is going on with you? What is this? What? What?
I dropped a little bit of weight. You know, Few problems getting older,
you know. Marcy.
Oh, Mom, I hope you don't mind. I brought Adam. Adam is my name.
Oh, I think I know who he is. How do you do? Welcome to the
church, Chandler. Thank you for having me. Girl, why didn't you
tell me you had a new man in your life?
Yes, you have no idea. This is going to be a wonderful Christmas.
Oh, Marcy, we. We can talk about Adam later.
You hungry? Yes. Well, come on then. You know your Uncle Donald's
waiting to see you. Your aunts are all in. Can't wait to get his behind.
Marcy, man,
seriously, no pressure.
No pressure. No, but she thinks I'm your boyfriend. Marcy,
I feel like you kind of had this whole thing planned out. See, I know
this was a bad idea. Adam, Adam,
calm down, okay? I will straighten this whole mess out.
We can just get back to work, okay? Really?
Absolutely.
Fine. You straighten it out. I will just. It's a
lot to take in. I mean, if I knew you were hiring a boyfriend,
I would have charged you double. I don't need to hire a boyfriend.