Wow, this guy is good. Uh huh. Where'd you find him?
Been using him for years. Hey, listen, can you forward me the rest
of those images from the presentation, please? I need to look. Check your pad.
Very nice. Brilliant.
I thought you'd like that. My God, where do you come up with this stuff?
You know, girl, I'm like, Mike. I like.
Which Mike? Which one? Yeah, all of
them. Oh. Jordan, Jackson,
Tyson. Okay. All right. Okay. Michael Buffer.
Okay, looks good. Thank you. No, listen,
it's getting no late. She. I have neighbors.
You don't want to hear it. Do you know what time it is? You neighbors
want to hear me? Stay with me. We're almost there. Here's what I want you
to do. If you could just add that value proposition piece back in, and then
instead of the pie chart, a little bar graph, you're good to go. Yes.
Gotcha. I got you. Can you imagine little old Jewel Advertising,
the agency of Recka for Clarion Candy? Yes, I can.
Yeah. Yeah. That's why you brought me in, right?
Yeah. You know what that means? What? It means
little Jewel is about to become big Jewel.
Yeah. Yeah. That's hot.
Nervous? No. Never.
Dang it. Why is Dana blowing me up right
now? Oh, hi. Hi, Dana.
Hi, sweetie. You wanna hear some really exciting news?
No, no, no. Absolutely not. Well, if you're busy.
Not you. I want glasses and two pictures.
Sorry. Oh, my God. Okay, so. I cannot
believe you just did that. Geez. Well, I said I was sorry,
not you. Mom, can you put this in the cabinet? Thank you.
Hang on. Just.
I'll be back in two seconds. Okay.
So where were we? Yeah, well, you know, I'm just preparing for
this huge presentation right now. I'm leaving the country.
Marcy, did you hear me? Did you just say you're. I'm leaving
the country. Frankie and I are going to Haiti for five years to do some
missionary work. And we're leaving right after Christmas. Wow,
that's great. It's wonderful. Hey, baby,
it's wonderful. But I don't know how often that we're
gonna be getting home, so I really wanna see you. Please tell
me you're coming home for Christmas this year. Dana, you know I
love you, but every time I come home. Yeah,
I know, third degree, but Marcy, I haven't seen you in years.
Why don't you come to New York? Marcy,
You know, I really wish I could, but I
just. I'm swamped right now. I have so much work to do. I'm.
You understand, right, Dana? Okay, I understand.
And you sound busy, so I'm gonna just let you go. And plus, they're messing
up the kitchen, and you know how I like things organized, so I'm gonna go.
Dana. It's okay. It's okay. Good luck
on your project, and I'll talk to you later.
Dana.