Yes. We did it, boss. We did it.
Congratulations. No, no, Adam, you did. I,
I was drowning in there. Hey, look, you know what I always say? Promise him
anything. We'll got the details later.
What's up? Remember how I said I hated going home
for Christmas? Yeah. Yeah. Well,
my favorite cousin, Dana.
Yes. Dana is leaving the country the day
after Christmas. She really wants me to come home. Uh,
wow. Bummer. What'd you tell her? I had to tell her I couldn't.
I have way too much work to do. That's true. That's true.
Yeah, but you know, she was just so disappointed.
She's always been there for me. I remember one
time when we were in the third grade, she got all up in Jimmy Strayhorn's
face because he put chocolate pudding in my hair. No, he didn't.
Yes, he did. And then when we were in the 10th grade,
we formed this two woman glee club. Cause neither one of us could sing well
enough allegedly, to be in the real glee club.
Really? Allegedly. I'm sure you're talented.
And then after we graduated college,
she came to visit me every single year on my birthday. And we
would have these. Sleep. Slumber party.
Yeah. But then all that stopped when. When you got too busy.
Got too busy? Yeah. Well, such is life.
Well, what I mean by that is she sounds really special.
And if it were me, I would drop everything
and try to see her before she left the country.
I'm just saying. You know what?
You are absolutely right. I'm going home for Christmas.
I'm going home for Christmas. Yep. You already promised
Dana, so there's no turning back now. Hey, maybe she hasn't told anyone
yet. Good luck with that. Um, great.
Is that your mom? No, you don't understand.
I cannot go home for Christmas. I, I, I have too much work to do.
Well, you're just gonna have to do it before you leave. That's not possible.
But I can't go back on the promise I made my cousin Dana. She'll never
forgive me.
Look, go home.
See you cousin. Take care of everything here. I'm not going anywhere anyway.
Oh, no way. I cannot put all this work on you. It's fine.
I don't go anywhere for the holidays. Yeah. No, no.
Oh, I got it. I got it. Come with me. Come with
me. Oh. Oh, yes, yes. We'll get all our work done down there,
and you can fly back home to Chicago from Atlanta. My treat.
Go on. Um, I,
I will double,
double, double your Christmas bonus.
And. And what?
You like peach cobbler? I love peach cobbler. Okay. The Chandler women
bake a mean peach cobbler. That's all I got. Deal,
ATL Here we go.