Yo, Kev. Where have you been, man? Yeah, yeah. Hang on, hang on.
I just came across an opportunity that fell in
my lap. Yeah? Yeah. Let's just say I'm working on
a really big account that's gonna put me back in the game. And, you know,
if I'm back in the game, you back in the game too, right?
Sorriest Christmas tree farm I've ever seen. Little old anemic tree.
I hope those guys don't make a living doing this. Otherwise,
the Chandler women are taking their beauty rest.
Well, then you, my dear, must get 40 winks every night.
Come here, baby. Oh,
boy.
Before you go to bed, where's Marcy and Wes's face? Everybody sleep,
baby. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Marcy's here?
Yeah, yeah, she got in today. Who is? Wes's face, man,
I don't know. What's his face is her new fiance.
At least that's what I've been told.
So Marcy's getting married? Yeah. Yeah, next Christmas.
About that time, don't you think? Yeah, it's big,
right? Yeah, I know. The Chandler women, they're ecstatic about it.
So I bet.
Hey, you want me to go up and get her? Man, I'm pretty sure that
she's up. I know she'd love to see you. Let me. Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. You getting seated out in your 30s? What?
Marcy hates me. Always has.
Okay? And you. You know,
me and your cousin never got along. Oh, yeah, yeah, I know.
Right? All right, no, fine. Okay. You used
to pull her hair when she was a little girl, right? You teased her all
through middle school. You ignored her during high school. You ridiculed everything she
did during college. All right? Yeah, like I said.
Mm, man, whatever. Where was your
big shot cousin Preston at? Oh, you know, he doesn't come into the grand finale.
You know, Christmas Day, maybe even New Year's Eve. So typical.
Oh, wait, stop. Are you serious? Are y' all still going at it?
Oh, yeah. It's gonna get a lot worse before it gets better. You about to
go? Yeah, man. I gotta get some work done. You still showing up for breakfast,
right? Come on, man, you know it. Oh, dude, don't bring Charlene.
Don't do that. Can you let that go? I'm just saying.