And now, church, a solo from our own Sister Chandler.
Sister, Come on. Give God some praise.
Hallelujah. Hallelujah.
Said the night went to the Little lamb
do you see what I see?
Way up in the sky sky Little lamb do
you see what I see? Away in
the manger gnome his head.
We wish you a merry Christmas we wish you a merry
Christmas we wish you a merry Christmas and a happy offer
Snowel.
Jingle bells, jingle bells Jingle all the way
oh, what one it is to ride in a one horse hold with
three kings A oriental
bearing gifts from so
far and deck the halted boughs
of holly FA la la la la la la la la Tis the season to
be jolly La la la la.
The stars are brightly shining
Ho. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa,
whoa,
whoa.
This concludes our Christmas concert.
Yeah. Nah, dude, couldn't be better. Yeah, I mean, I had a
couple speed bumps along the way, but nothing I can't handle,
huh? No, it'll be fine as soon as I get out of this one horse
town. Yeah, yeah. No, I promise you Marcy's gonna make
me her partner in more ways than one. Yeah, we'll get to finally run
a successful ad agenc for a change. I gotta
get back in here, man. Gotta join hands with the family and sing Christmas carols.
I know.
Hey, Mars, can I. Can I holler at you for a minute? Oh, sure.
I'll meet you at the car, okay? Okay. Okay.
See you later. What's going on?