O come let us adore him
oh come let us adore him.
Christ the Lord it
is. Actually, it's been so long since I've been to one of these I've forgotten
how awesome they are. Oh no.
I'll be right back. Enjoy the concert. Christ the
Lord.
Hi, Judy, are you there? Hi.
Yeah, I'm sorry, I was inside my mom's console.
Uh huh. Yes, yes. No,
I realize that, but it's Christmas and so.
Oh no, no, no, no, no. I definitely value your business.
Of course, no question. Okay.
Okay. Well then I can have that to you tomorrow morning.
Tonight. Okay,
sure, no problem. I'll shoot it over to you tonight.
Okay. All right, listen, have a marry Chris.
Uh, uh, uh. The demanding life of a
big time ad exec and of a small town lawyer.
Ah, here we go. Tell me, how do you
represent everybody in town? I mean, what happens when you have two
clients who are at odds with each other? Well, that's actually happened,
believe it or not. I just basically help them
figure out a way to resolve the differences. It's not that hard.
Gotcha. So what about you? I mean there's
gotta be some moral stuff that comes up in your line of work. No,
no, no, no, not really. I try to separate my personal beliefs from
my business responsibilities. I mean, my job is to sell products, services and ideas.
I don't legislate morality. That's not what I do.
Well, it's obviously served you well. You seem to be pretty successful.
You say that like it's a bad thing. In fact, everyone in this
town seems to resent me cause I'm focused on my career.
If you were a man, no one would care. Right?
Exactly. Double standards.
But to be honest with you Marcy, I don't really think anybody in this town
begrudges you anything. Especially not just a. I mean, I don't.
I just think people that love you want to
be a part of your life. Are you saying that you
are happy for my success? Why wouldn't I be?
You know, I was, I was surprised at how well you did on the Chandler
Women Challenge. I didn't, I didn't. I couldn't believe you
really remembered all that about me. Now what would be so hard to believe that
I. I mean, come on. Yeah, I guess you
have no idea. You know what,
I'm gonna get inside. Okay? Okay, I'll be in in two seconds.
Marcy. Yeah? When you left
and tried to forget about everything and everybody. It doesn't
mean everyone else forgot about you, Far from.