All I'm saying is, I don't know why you Chandler women have to wait until
the week before Christmas to get a dadggone treat. Because it's tradition,
honey, all the sisters have to agree. It's been like that since we were little.
And it's not about to change. Now. Tell me, sis. Now, who wants to say
grace? And where's Marcy? Well, here's Adam. Adam, where's your betrothed?
I believe she is finishing up a conference call. A conference call? My daughter's gonna
be late for her own funeral. Marcy. Hey, man, what's up?
I'm Frankie. I am Marcy's favorite cousin in law
dog. Call him Doc,
Everybody. Hey, you precious
Doc. Aw, Donald.
How you doing? You too. Being engaged certainly
becomes you. Well, I certainly won't argue with you.
Oh, you know what? That is my big surprise
for you, Marcy. You have a surprise for me? Okay. I like blue boxes.
What's up? In. Come on in. What's up? Family?
Blair. Ms. Stephanie.
Marcy. Blair. Blair Kirkland.
What brings you to town? I never left. You know
me, big fish, small pond kind of guy, right?
Unlike you. Yeah. No, totally big fish,
totally big pond. Here we go. Yeah.
So, what have you been doing with yourself? You working? Are you in school?
School? I'm still an attorney, Marcy. All right,
I completely forgot. Say grace. Okay,
food's getting cold. Everyone bow heads. Food's getting cold.
Bless us, O Lord. Marcy. Bless us, O Lord,
for thy food which we're about to receive from thy bounty through Christ our
Lord. Amen. Amen. So, Marcy, are you going to
introduce me to your fiance? What? Adam.
Adam, dear, I think Blair wants to be introduced to your fiance.
Adam. Right, Adam. Um, Adam, this is Blair.
Blair, this is my fiance, Adam.
Congratulations, bro. Good luck.
Adam, we have to go shopping later for engagement
rings, remember? Yeah.
Yes. Oh, yeah.
So, Adam, what line of work are you in? I'm an
ad man. Blair. Oh, what a coincidence. So is Marcy.
Yeah, I know. We work. He works with
my company. Oh, so you two are partners?
No, she's his boss.
Oh, well, that's convenient.
Adam, we should go. I haven't eaten any.
That's okay. We can heat it up later. I'll take you a little package.
Oh, okay. Marcy. Hey, I hope you guys don't mind.
I invited Charlene over for dinner. What? Charlene?
Charlene Berman.
Charlene, everybody. Everybody's in. Charlene.
Charlene Berman. Well, look at what the
cat dragged in. Mousy Jewel,
I haven't had this much fun since divorce court.
So good to see you again. Oh, yes. Yellow.
Thank you.