This is just like old times, huh? Cereal for breakfast,
cereal for lunch, cereal for dinner. All day.
I am so glad you came home, Marcy.
Yeah, I am too. I just can't believe you
are leaving the country. Five years, Dana. No,
I can't believe you have a fiance and you didn't even tell me about him.
Come on, Dana Dane, you know why I couldn't say anything to you. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, I know. You don't want to get henpecked about getting married. Well,
come on, I wouldn't have said anything to anyone.
Okay, maybe Frankie. Yeah, maybe Frankie and
everybody else. Frankie would have told. Come on.
Mmm. I've missed you, cuz.
I miss you too. But you know I'm doing
my thing in New York. Yeah. No. Meetings, presentations,
conference calls. Yeah, I know.
Well, maybe Adam can get you to slow down and think about
family. I'm really happy that you found someone. You two seem
really happy. Yeah. How long have you
known Adam? Uh, three. No,
I'm sorry, I'm tired. Nine. Um. A year.
Yeah, a year. Mm, mm, mm, mm. What is
it that you're not telling me? What? Nothing. Marcy, you know you always play
with your earrings when you're lying, right? What's going on? Listen, what's going
on is I really need to know what's going on with my mother. Somebody's looking
for mommy. Hi. Hi.
Hi, auntie. Hi, baby. Oh, wow.
I better take this actually. Hi, it's Marcy.
Uh huh. Yes.
Hey. Got it over here. I think I see some good ones. Okay.
It's cold out here. It's a little chilly. What's wrong with this one?
This is it. Oh, no, no, no. If you bring that little twig to
the Chandler women, you will be sleeping outside in Smokey's old quarters.
Smokey? Marcia's favorite dog as a child. I'm surprised
y' all haven't talked about that, being engaged and all. Here you go.
Come on, man, let's go catch up with Uncle Donald. Yeah, you know we talk,
right? You talk about all kind of stuff. Yeah, we were just talking yesterday.
I can't believe we struck out again. Man, are we in trouble.
Why don't you just save the trouble and get the tree from Walmart?
Never mind. You don't even know, do you? How the whole
Chandler women Christmas tree hunt got started?
Marcy, she was a kid, right? Guys Must have been what, five or six?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. And they had this really small tree and Marcie got
up on her tippy toes trying to get a candy cane. And the whole tree
fell down on top of her. It was hilarious. And ever since then, she demanded
that they get a perfect tree. A tree big enough that her or her
cousins couldn't topple. That's a
good story. You know, Blair, I keep forgetting. How long have you been the president
of Marcy's fan club? Uh. Oh. Oh. Hey, easy, bro.
Look, man, me, Blair, Dana, Marcy, we all went to school together, okay? We grew
up together. So? So just take it easy. Stop hating. No, I'm not hating.
It's cool. I mean, me and Marcy, we just fine.
We just. We just fine. Yeah. Yeah. I gotta go.
Okay. You know, me and Marcy have a business to run.
Wow. LL fool J boy. Kind of sensitive.
Me and Marcy have a business to run.
I don't like him. I don't like him. He's all right. He's just from New
York and he's short. Yeah, he's from New York.