Okay. Yes.
Cuz, I gotta give it to you. You got his nose wide open. Your boy
acting like he a little jealous. Okay, what happened? Hey, let him tell you.
Can I come in?
Clarion loved the composites. That's great.
How did the Christmas tree hunt go?
You know, your friend Blair is a real jerk. I could have told you that.
Yeah. You got a thing for you or something, Blair?
No. We actually kind of hate each other. Why? What happened?
Nothing. It's just. Got a big
mouth. Adam, are you jealous?
Jealous? Excuse. Marcie, you are my boss.
This is a game. No reason to be jealous,
right? Right. Why would you be jealous?
Um. Look,
remember that game you were talking about us playing where we get to know each
other better? Right? Yeah. I think we should. We should do that. It could be
good for us. Okay. Yeah. Yeah,
I think I like that. Yeah. Yeah.
Good. Let's play.
No Christmas tree again. Pathetic.
Unbelievable. Men.
What did you expect? Listen. Well, hold on, ladies. Relax,
okay? We tried. Might I make a suggestion? Why don't the
Chandler women go out and find a tree that the Chandler women
can agree on? That way the Chandler women can be happy.
Oh, don't think we can't do it. And don't you think we won't do
it. Yes, we will. As a matter of fact, that's exactly what we're going to
do, ladies. We're going to select a superlative Christmas tree. We're gonna decorate it.
Trust and believe. We will do a much better job than the man.
Is that so? Okay, we'll see about that. Tell you what. Men versus
women. Whoever finds the best tree win your honor wins What?
Daddy. Oh, wait a minute. I got it. Okay, so loser
has to bring the tree in, set it up and decorate it all on their
own. But you only get to choose three people to help you do it.
That's what I'm talking about. I don't like the way you looked over here when
you said loser. Oh, I was addressing it to everybody. But if you want to
pick it. Deal? Deal. Deal. Deal. Deal. All right,
all right. Whatever. Name? Stephanie. Deal. Right.
Handshake. Oh, they got a secret little hand.
Oh, man.