Okay.
Smells good. Morning, baby.
I look a little tired. We up all night? Yeah, something like
that. I thought I heard a little something last night. You and Adam
having Fine.
Oh, I don't think so.
What in the devil.
Did I just. You want to help
me make another cobbler, babe? I would love to. Cinnamon in the bowl, please.
Okay. How much? Just a dash.
That's not a dash, babe. That's. What was that? Three taps is
a dash. It's a dash. Well, now it's in there. I can't
do anything now.
Hey.
Probably not a good idea to sneak up on people at the cemetery. You know,
I'm sorry. Sorry?
Oh, you know, it's my first time here in four years.
It's not an easy place to come to. No, it's not.
But I'm actually glad I came. I mean, I know my dad's not here,
but. I know what you mean. I come out
here for the same reason.
Marcy, I.
I wanted to apologize for your. No, no, no,
don't. Turns out you were right about
Adam. He left this morning.
Well, this is the part where you get to gloat.
For once, I wish I was wrong.
Sort of.
Can we talk? Yeah. Let's get out of this weather.
Okay.