Breon, come on in here. I got one more gift.
Candy. You know what? You gotta ask your mom about that.
Do you know how she is about the cavities? One. One. Yes.
Girl, granddaddy gonna give you two candies.
Yes. Your mama don't know what she talking about. Be quiet. Good for you.
Hey, how you doing? Okay. It's okay.
Hey, what's going on? All right, now.
I know what I said. I know what I said. Thank you.
So what? Go. You are so just.
Why are you in my business? Why are you such a sweet.
Go.
Merry Christmas, baby. Oh, hey. Merry Christmas,
Charlene. You look great. Thank you. Hi, everyone. Merry Christmas.
Merry. Merry Christmas, Mousey. Marcie,
right? Honey, I have your present back
at my house. What do you say that you and I just go back and.
You know, I promised Ms. Stephanie that I will spend some time with
everybody. Oh, well, miss so busy here,
I'm sure that she won't even miss you. Yeah.
I'm just not ready to go yet, Charlene.
Well, I am. Well,
I guess you gotta do what you gotta do and go.
Go. Well, maybe I'll go without
This is where I wanna be, Charlene.
You2bit Mayberry lawyer.
Wait. Shut up. Really?
What's in that? What key? Nothing,
man. Ain't that what you wanted? Yeah. Okay. All right.
Get back to the fish store. I know one thing.
I see my wife. I'm glad
I can be. Hey, I'm going to. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where you going? Just, just let it go, D. Where you going? Yeah.
Oh, what's up? You know,
I, I, I wanted to talk to you because there I.
There when we. Hey, Marcy, you're a person.
Just say.