Okay, now that I have everyone's
attention, I actually have a confession that I
need to make. What is it, baby?
Adam and I weren't really engaged. Okay, I know.
I know it's kind of crazy, but we were faking
it the whole time because I didn't want you to be
giving me a hard time.
You already knew that. Look, Marcie, we may not
have seen you in years, but we know you. After a while, it was just
plain as day to everyone except Blair. Blair. Poor Blair.
What do you expect from a 2 bit Mayberry attorney?
I am so sorry that you felt the only way
that you welcomed home by your family, by me, is if you pretended
to do what I wanted you to do. No, mom, not you. It's me.
I'm the one who should be sorry. I haven't been home in forever,
and now you're sick. And it's not.
Mom is. She's having blood tests. She has pains that
I had the routine blood work for my annual checkup. That's all. And as
for the illness, little injury
with the knee and the ankle, a little bit on the back.
Sell us a lesson. What? So, son, who are these gentle
women? Laugh. Why? I hope you know what you're getting yourself into. Really, Mom?
Don't listen to Uncle Donald. Baby, I am so sorry you've been
worried about me all this time. I love you. I love you too.
Mamas. We're proud of you. Really proud. We love you
so much. Thank you. I don'. I don't care if you
ever get married. I don't care if you ever have kids. All that matters is
that I have my baby home for Christmas every Christmas.
Uh, Ms. Stephanie? Yes. Could I say something,
Marcy Leanne Chandler Jewell.
I'm pretty sure I've loved you my whole life.
And I want to love you for the rest of my life.
Marcy, will you marry me?
Yes, I'll marry you.
Before y' all get to kiss. Let me get the mistletoe. Liddy.
I do not need a mistletoe for this, bub.
Okay, everybody. Everybody, how about. How about a round
of Christmas carol, Daddy? Okay, okay.
Wish you a merry Christmas we wish you a
merry Christmas we wish you a merry Christmas A
happy New year.