What is your least favorite food?
Least? Oh, hot dogs. Hot dogs. Oh, yeah. Everybody loves hot dogs.
Oh, no. Fourth of July cookout, my Aunt Myra's
house. I choked on a hot dog. Almost died, actually. Yeah,
I've hated them ever since. Wow. And who cooked that? Was that Aunt Myra?
I think it was Uncle Donald, actually. Really crispy
on the end.
All right. What about you Biggest disappointment?
Oh, when my
agency folded, it was.
It was a dream of mine and Kevin. Since college was
all we. All we dreamed about,
all we cared about. So when it
folded, I don't know. Okay,
switching subjects. Mm. What is your favorite cartoon?
Ooh, Pokey Pig. Without a doubt. Pookie Pig.
Yes. That's all, folks. I mean, come on. How adorable is that?
Oh, that's a great impression. Thank you. I might take that on the road
for a short trip. Come wise.
Freaking pants. All right. Okay, Mr. Smarty Pants. Your dream
car, make it a good one.
My dream car is a 1958 Alfa Romero
Gulero Spider. Oh, okay. Now I see why you
can criticize my impressions. Cause you're so good. No hate. That was
good. No hate. Yeah, that was good. Oh,
all right. Mm. Um.
Wow. What else? What else? Okay,
here's a biggie. Mm. What is your biggest fear?
Mm. I have to go. Get all serious on
me. My biggest fear? Yeah. No judgment, no judging.
What is that? Scout's honor. This is Scout's honor. Scout's honor. Is that.
Were you even a Scout? I don't think that's right. That'll look accurate to me.
I was the Scout Chief leader. I was, uh, Chief.
Really? Stop stalling,
Failure. Failure. Yeah. Yeah,
I am. I have this. I have this fear
that, you know, I'll wake up one day and be 80
years old and not have accomplished anything that I set
out to accomplish, and my life will just be one big swap.
I was kind of expecting you to say spiders.
Clowns. Yeah. You know what? I don't like spiders either,
come to think of it. And clowns frighten me,
for sure. But you know what?
Actually, I'm kind of a big scaredy cat underneath it
all. Well, yeah, no, no. I don't believe that for one second. See, you're a
bulldog, just like me. You see an opportunity, you see, you go after it,
and you take it. That's courage. That's strength.
I need to write that one. You better write
it down. And you better give me credit. What? Oh, my God.
Are you serious right now? I don't like dogs. I don't like dogs. That's a
Chihuahua. That's a big Chihuahua. Oh,
my. Okay. It's like a monster. Now I see who you really are.
Okay, Now I know what your fear is,
little mousy dogs.