Where's Marcy? Oh, God, Liz, I told you to put on your sweater already.
You're shooting a. Damn it. Oh, stop fibbing, Mom. I am not wearing your
sweater. They smell like mothballs. Where do you think I packed those sweaters?
Adam, get in the car. You're riding with the men. You're driving, baby. You're driving,
baby. Liz. Hey, hey, hey, hey. You in the back. But I'm not gonna sit
in the middle. Get in the car. It's too fabulous to be in the middle.
And I'm not sitting on the hump. Get in. Get in the car. Who's driving?
Oh, my God. There's the keys.
Oh, come on. Where's Bria?
Hey, Bria, come get in the car with Daddy, honey. Here he comes. Here I
come. All right. Look at you. You look so nice.
Okay, ladies, we're gonna split up and meet back here in 45 minutes to report
our findings. Are you ready? Yep.
Mom. Wait, wait, wait. Mom, I got you, okay?
Oh, well, because you. I. We can't all go by
ourselves. Like, what are you gonna do? If I
had been around. Oh, okay. Can you slow down? Honey,
why are you treating me like an invalid? I've been hobbling on this ankle
for weeks. You would have known. Well, that would have. Oh, had I been home,
I would have known. Or better yet, I could have helped. I wasn't gonna say
that. Yeah, but you were thinking it, Marcie. Honey, I was not. Well, you know
what? I'm not gonna lie with you, Marcy. I can't tell you how many times
I have wanted you here. How many times I've wanted you here for
my birthday, for Mother's Day, for Christmas.
Had to make up all kinds of excuses because of you. What excuses? Mom?
I was working. Working, work, work. We're always putting work before family.
Marcy, did you not turn around for me? Now, you look at me. You brought
it up. And I am going to finish. Marcie, I have missed
my daughter. Do you understand me? Baby,
I know that I probably got on your last nerve talking about getting married.
I understand. And having children. But I need you to be honest with
yourself and with me. Is that the only reason?
Hmm? The only reason why you stayed away for so long?
I better get going. My Aunt Myra's gonna be blowing
that blasted whistle in another 45 minutes.
I'm coming.