Really? Oh, Walt. I'm sorry,
Marcy. Yeah, yeah, Marcy. My bad.
Do not tell me you got the perfect Christmas tree tracker in that phone.
Ha ha ha. Funny.
You know, these Christmas traditions can become
a little silly, right? No. I mean, opening presents,
spending time with family, eggnog at midnight. What could be better than that?
Okay, so you mean to tell me you were in New York all this time
doing all those things with Adam? Oh, and you were out
here getting all cozy with Charlene? Okay, I only ask because
you. It's been so long since you've been home, I figured life out of New
York must be real sweet. Hey, listen, you got something you want to get off
your chest, Mr. Lawyer Man? I mean, spit it
out. Better yet, why don't you do us all a favor and go spend Christmas,
you know, with my family?
That's what you were gonna say? I'm sorry. My mother. I'm.
That's not what I was gonna say. You know,
when you didn't call, I just. I didn't think you knew.
My mother told me, and I told her to tell you.
What? What, you didn't have time to tell me yourself?
Your condolences? She did, and I
told her to tell you. Thank you. So thank