I am dying.
Holy God.
Holy child.
No. As I was saying, why don't we get out of here and go back
to my office? I was going back to the office to get some work done.
I'll come by later on. You said that
last night. I know,
Charlene, but this case is just getting crazy. I expect to see you at my
house in one hour, Blair Kirkland. Otherwise don't bother coming at all.
Wonderful. Thank you very much.
Let everyone know I say goodnight. Oh, sure. Better run home now.
All right. Have it on my desk in the morning. All right. Ah,
Blair. Preston. How are you? I'm well.
Merry Christmas. Likewise,
Preston. Cuz,
what's up? Look at you. Look at you. Stand back. Let me look at you.
Look, Preston. I see you. Adam Reed. All right. How you doing?
Adam is my right hand man at the agency. Ah.
Oh. All right, all right. Slow down. All right, all right. And. Oh, oh,
and my fiance.
Congratulations. Thank you. PS1. I see.
Ah, that would be VVS. Oh, excuse me. Very very.
Did it set you very, very back? I. I'm doing okay.
Listen, no one's been able to tie this one down. You must tell me how
you did that one day. I will. Over drinks.
You don't. No problem. I'll have the office set it up. Listen, Marsh, you can't
keep on Stephie waiting. You know you can't avoid her singing all night. So stop
it. Let's go. Okay, I'll be right there. I'll be right there.
I don't know. I know.
What the heck was that? I don't know. I think your mom needs singing list.
I'm not talking about my mother. I'm talking about you. You are fawning over
him like a little family. I wasn't fawning all over anybody. Now that's
your. Your family, Your cousin. I'm trying to be nice. Yes, he's my cousin,
but we're not that close. Well, if you're not that close, maybe somebody should have
told him that before he dropped a million dollar contract in your lap. Marcy.
Marcy, would you please come help me sing this song? These people cannot sing to
save their lives. I'll be right there, Mom. Forget you. Say you give a woman
some sheet music and a solo and she thinks she's Jennifer Hudson and Patti LaBelle
and Rihanna. Great. It's Judy from
Clarion. Candy. Does she not know it's 9 o' clock at night? Go be
with your family. I'll take it. Oh my God. This is insane.
Okay. All right. Thank you. I'm coming, Mother.
Hey, Judy. Adam Reed. Yeah,
I'm Marcy's partner. Well, she's a little tied up right now, so I'll
be handling things with you directly.