Do I understand? No, I will, I promise.
It's just a little. Yeah, I'm on the
right side. Yeah, I will. Thank you. Bye. Bye.
Morning, honey. Morning. Aw, morning.
How'd you sleep? That bed is way
too comfortable. Is that a new mattress? You hungry? You know,
I'm not really. Blueberry pancakes. Still like them, right?
I do. I do have the 90s. Is blueberry pancake.
There you go, sweetie. Thank you. You know, mom, I wanted to apologize to you.
Oh honey, you don't need to apologize. I completely forgot you cannot sing
your way out of a paper bag. Why would I apologize for my
singing? No, honey, anything you want to
apologize for you can wait till after Christmas. Uh huh. Absolutely.
And we have the same goals, Mr.
Morty. Right, Judy? I couldn't agree with you more.
Right, we'll get right on it. You sweet on Adam?
Just like I was with your father.
I especially miss him this time of year though.
Yeah, yeah, I miss him too, Mom.
Have you been over to the cemetery?
You know, just put some flowers on his grave, honey?
Mom, it's been a little while, you know.
I know, mom. You know, I'm just.
Huh. I'm not really good at that kind of
thing. I'll get there. All right, we'll tell Adam
to get off the phone. Pancakes are almost ready. Okay? Okay. Oh,
it looks fine. It was. It was like that. Always like that in the first
place, which is fine. Marcy, honey, your aunties are here.
Auntie's here to pick us up. Let's go. Mom, I'm actually preparing for a
conference. Call the clients. I can't. Conference call? Honey, don't you remember? We have to
make cookies for game night. Plus get the ingredients for the peach cobbler.
Peach gobbler. The famous Chandler women's peach gobbler. That's right. I promise
I will be done and ready for the baking and the games. Please, can you
just go without me? You know, Marcy, if you want to go with your mom,
I can take care of the conference call. Yeah, but I haven't spoken to Judy
in two days. I don't want her to think I'm. No, no, Marcy, Judy's fine.
She's up to speed. I've been talking to her. She's fine. I mean, unless you
don't trust me to. Of course I trust you.
All right, mom, let me get my things and I'll be right out. I'll see
you in the car. Okay. Ryder, stop blowing that horn. You're gonna wear it out.
Yeah, just go have fun. With your family. Oh, God.
I'm really sorry to put all this work on you. A lot. That's what I'm
here for. Yeah. Hey, listen, when you get back, maybe we could
sneak away, do some Christmas shopping of our own. If you want to.
Okay. Yeah, I think I'd like that. Okay. I already got the
Walmart picked up. Sneak away to Walmart.
See you soon. Okay. Have fun.