Jingle bells, jingle bell.
Oh, it's about time you two love birds showed up.
Thank you, Marcie, for coming back in time to help us with the baking,
with the cooking. Thank you. Sorry I missed that.
Well, all I know is I cleaned up. I got CDs, DVDs, clothes, everything.
Razor. Sounds like you worked up an appetite. I did work up
an appetite. So where is the peach cobbler? It's right here. But you can't have
any till Christmas Day. How about the cookies? So is there
anything here for me? I'm surprised you're still speaking
to me. I know you're a jerk.
I got that player. Appreciate that. Thank you.
All right, you two. You see it? Pucker it on up.
Oh, well, you don't have to
tell me twice.
Ooh. That's what I'm talking about. All right.
Okay, okay. That's what I call working up an appetite. Somebody give that boy a
plate. And you, young man, bring that mistletoe hither.
I got you, Daddy. Come here, baby. Don't get too crazy. Come here,
baby. Come here, baby. Uh. Oh.
Hey. All right.
That's what I'm talking about.
Mom, what's in that glass? How do you take. No. Yes. But what
else? Old stuff. I mean, thank you.
Hey, Marcy. Sorry about before.
Just do what I had to do. Yeah, you. You did what you had to
do. That's. You didn't mind.
Did What? You kissing me. No. Did you?
Did you mind kissing me? No,
I didn't mind it. Actually, I kind of liked it.
Okay, I liked it a little bit.
My bad. Excuse me, y'. All. All right, so anyway,
the object of this game is to find out who knows the most about a
particular Chandler woman. Hence the name Chandler
Women Challenge. All right, now, I ain't come up with that name. The sisters did.
So I think we should do my Dana. I will. Dana. No, I think
we should do me. Definitely not. Let's do Marcy.
Oh, yeah. Let's not do Marcy. No, let's not do Marcy. I mean,
she's been gone forever. No one's going to remember anything about her. Do you?
No. Let's do Marcy. It'll be fine.