What's that supposed to mean? Nothing, nothing. It's just a joke.
Maybe you'd have got it if I sent it via text or email.
Maybe.
I know what you're trying to do. You're trying to bait me into an argument.
Mm. But I'm not gonna go for it. What's up your butt? We are
disconnected, Omar. Like, seriously. I mean, I've said it before, but you don't
get it. Our communication sucks. Okay?
You said we're disconnected. Okay, so. So you
wanna communicate? Okay, if you wanna communicate, let's communicate.
I can't remember the last time you asked me how Wright's investments was doing.
Okay. How's your business going?
Oh, it's great, honey. It'd be even better if my wife was a little bit
more supportive of me. You need
me to be more supportive of you? Did I really just hear you say that
right? Yeah, you heard me. I mean, come on. When's the last time you came
up to the office and helped around? Excuse me? When was the last time I
was even invited to your office? Carmen, come on.
I mean, you really gotta be invited up. You can just come. That just goes
to prove that you've been slacking. Slacking?
Wow. Really? Who helped start your
business from the ground up? Cause it sure as the hell wasn't a slacker.
Did a slacker pay the mortgage and all the other bills for a year and
a half when you started your business? Did a slacker do your business proposal,
prepare your paperwork for three years before you could even afford to hire someone?
I'm sorry, is that not supportive? I didn't say you weren't supportive.
Okay, you wanna know what my problem is? It's the rolling of the eyes,
the sucking of the teeth every time I have to go on my phone,
or whether it rings or you trippin out when I come home late. It's like
you have a problem with the success of me and my business. No, I have
a problem with the fact that. That we don't spend quality time together, Omar.
And I don't think that's asking too much. Seriously, it's like you
have a better relationship with your electronic devices than you do with your own wife.
What are you talking about? You have too many distractions in your life,
plain and simple. Look, all I need from you
is some more attention, and I need some more time. That's it.