Listen, I really appreciate this and all, but how
about that dinner we talked about? Okay, this isn't a breakfast date,
August. It's just leftovers. Just, you know, not made for you specifically.
Just me being thoughtful little my Southern hospitality.
Um, dinner.
You keep stressing this dinner thing. That's because dinner ain't never
killed nobody. Well, I watched the news and it's gotten a couple people killed.
Dinner? Yes, dinner. And don't make me beg. Cause it don't look
good on my resume.
Okay, well, it's just dinner.
Mm. Just dinner? Yeah, I mean, I've been
stressed a lot, so. Could use a night on the town. Why not?
It's just dinner. Yeah, let's. Let's do dinner.
But we're gonna do a Dutch. Please. Dutch is not an option.
Oh, come on. Isn't that what the cool kids do these days? It's not an
option, lady. Okay, but you cannot
come pick me up here. Okay? That would not be a good idea with Mr.
Wright. Seven o'. Clock. Seven it is.
Tell you what, I'm gonna text you a time and a
location in about an hour. Okay? All right,
let's shake on it.
You all right with me?