Okay, talk to you soon.
Woo. Karina,
sweetheart, I would like to thank you again on a job well done.
Uh huh. You rock. You know, Peter still hounded me about that
answer from you. I'm gonna take it.
You are? Mm. Yep. I already put my house on
the market, so if you know anyone who's looking for a five bedroom house in
Buckhead. Okay. Let him know about my place. Duly noted.
Well, then I guess I should thank you for leaving me with all of your
clients here. Ain't no problem. You know, I think you're gonna be great. You know,
they're gonna really like you. Oh, I know. A lot of great value.
So thank you. I couldn't have done it without you.
Thank you. Mm.
Yeah,
I should probably go. Uh,
yeah, Yeah, I gotta go. To what?
It's happy hour downstairs at the cafe. Yeah.
Grab a drink. Or too soon? No, that sounds
great. That's that. Yeah. Okay, well, let me close up here and I'll hit you
in a minute. Okay. Okay. Okay, cool.
Hey. Wow.
I haven't seen you dressed like that in a long time. Where you going?
Just out. Out where?
To dinner.
Say you bought a new dress just to go to dinner. No,
Omar, this dress has been in the closet for a very
long time actually. Oh,
I just never seen you wear it. You've never given me a reason
So who you going to dinner with? Just a
friend. The girls? No, with a
guy friend.
God. Okay, look,
I'm allowing you to stay here till you get your place situated,
but I will not let you disrespect me. Oh, no disrespect.
Mm. Mm. But how was your breakfast meeting with Karina?
That was business, Carmen. Besides, I told you who I was having breakfast with.
I mean, you really think I'm gonna be cool with you going to dinner with
some dude dressed like that? Dressed like what? Look, I told you
I can stay at a hotel. Would you like me to stay at a hotel?
Man, do whatever you gotta do. I don't need you to tell me that I'm
grown. Not to mention almost single since you signed those stupid divorce
papers. Okay, you acting real out of pocket right now.
Here we go. Yeah, here we go.