Okay, I didn't plan that.
You did. I think you did plan it. Babe, it's business. Okay,
okay, I got it. It's business. Whatever. Answer it. You want to answer it anyway.
Radiation to the brain.
Wait. Now, you know, there was a study done that pets can improve
marriages and relationships. Maybe. Maybe you guys should consider getting
one since you're having issues conceiving. Samira, did you forget? I'm allergic
to cats and he's allergic to dogs. So we can't even get a pet?
I got it. A romantic vacation,
sandy beaches, little bikinis. Ooh,
I can't even remember the last time we did one of those. Okay, well,
then here's what you do. Just pack his clothes and throw it
in a trunk, okay? And then tell him that you want to go somewhere driving
or something, and then just mysteriously end up at the airport on your way to
Tahiti. That's how you do it. Tahiti. Yes. I like
that idea. Yes. But if it doesn't work, Samir, I'm fine. My butt to divorce
court. Mm. Mm. Y' all find it funny? I don't find it funny. Just a
little joke. All right? You need to get
on that vacation. Yes. And force that excitement and that adventure right
out of that black man. You can do it. That's what I'm talking about.
That's what I'm talking about. Talking about. Shoot. Make me want to
go home to my husband and just get it in.
Omar and I, we. We haven't
gotten it in a couple of months. Was that months with
an S? Like, plural? Was it with an
S? Yes. That's a shock value. More than two? Cause it's working. Its shock
value is definitely working. No, I'm so serious. Like, I'm dead serious.
Yeah. I mean, don't judge me with those faces.
Well, you guys get eight years in your relationship, and, I mean,
I guess marriages sometimes just get rocky. Well, you know, I had
my issues with my husband. I mean,
I was gonna do something really bad. Like, really,
really bad. I was gonna be on a special edition to 48 hours. Like.
Yes. I mean, I was facing 25 to life on principle alone.
But what did you do? You put on that cape and you came and saved
Damon's life. That's what you did. Took all the guns and knives out my
house. But you did that for us.
And I just know you can get through this with ease. Yes, girl.
Yes. Look, you and Omar have been a
great example for me and Jihad. Wow.
I didn't know you guys felt that way. Yeah. Well, listen,
heifers, it's time for you to put on your capes. Well, then,
girlfriends, superheroes to the restaurant, you die.
Exactly. I love y'. All.
Mmm. This is good.
I appreciate you coming home early for dinner.
You know, I heard you the other night. I was listening, and you're right.
I'm sorry. Thanks, babe.
So, I was thinking. We have not been on a vacation
in quite a while, right? And the girls and I just happen to be talking
about Tahiti. What do you think about that? It's dope. Tahiti sounds
dope. Yeah, I don't mess with Tahiti. You know, as long as they got wiper,
I'm good. Oh, gosh, I'm playing. It's okay.
I mean, is there someplace else you'd rather go?
I always go back to Cancun. I don't think we're allowed back here.
We've been banned from a couple of places. Yeah, we have. Miami beach,
spring break. Okay, let me just say, you was
out of control that balcony. Not my fault. Well, you in that dark liquor.
I can't handle my dark liquor. Yeah, that's why your booze came out.