It's not. I mean, it's not what I mean, it's not what I'm saying.
I see it. Yeah, yeah, you got the little side piece joint. You got the
side joint. No, I love Carmen.
To tell you the truth, I can't even remember the last time we got busy.
What? What's that? Can't remember.
That's not cool. That's no bueno, dude. That's no good,
homie. That's bad. That's real bad. No married man
should go three days without having sex with his
wife. Mm. Mm. Real talk. I'm just keeping it real. You asked me when's the
last time me and Jasmine did it. I'm gonna be like, about an hour ago.
Yeah, you asked me when we doing it again. I'm gonna be like, as soon
as she pick me up, we gonna stop at the McDonald's. Look, D, I don't
want to hear about your sex life with you and your wife. All right,
all right, look, I don't care about what you do with your wife. And.
And I don't care what you do with your wife, all right? I've been focusing
on my business, and that's probably the reason why I haven't been thinking about sex.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. If you having problems down
there, I mean, you should start by changing your diet. Try. They got pills.
Organic. Oh, yeah. Okay, you guys don't get it. Check your email. No, I'm just
saying. Look, it don't matter if you eating organic lima beans or you getting baby
back ribs. Tap that tonight.
What are you doing?
You know, this is our thing. Oh, I think.
Almost didn't recognize it since I haven't seen it in months.