So what you saying? You want to make love to your husband? Of course I'd
like to make love to my husband. But my husband's been doing a piss poor
job of showing his wife that he loves her.
What? I mean, we can't even have a simple conversation at dinner
and you don't pay me attention on a regular basis, yet all of a sudden
you want some boy? You need to try way harder than that. My God,
it's like I don't know who you are anymore. Like. And for you to insinuate
I don't love you is insane. Well, then I guess I'm insane because that's how
I feel. Omar, you drive a luxury car, you have all
these fancy clothes, you got a successful husband, you don't have to want for anything,
okay? You live a comfortable life. That's comfortable.
I don't give a damn about any of that. Babe. What happened
to flowers and cards for no reason just because?
Weekly date night. Intimate, passionate kisses that led
to hours of love making. What happened to that girl?
This ain't no romance novel. This is the real life right here.