So you put it down, he fell back in
love, and your marriage is saved, right? I don't know.
I woke up this morning, he was already gone for work. But I do love
that man. That is so obvious.
But what do you want Omar to do? I want him to fight.
Fight for me, fight for our marriage. The same way he fought for his company
to be where it is today. So why are you going through with this divorce?
I didn't think he'd actually sign the papers.
Stop. Don't laugh. Yeah, no, he called your bluff.
Yes, he called my bluff, but I didn't know what else to do. I felt
like. I felt like I was at my wit's end. All I can
say is we're here for you. So you guys.
You guys think it was wrong for me to make him sign the papers?
Uh, yes, ma'. Am. You were dead wrong.
You ambushed the man. It was like a mob hit.
He didn't even know what to do. I'm sorry. You know what?
We're not here to beat you up. We're here to build you up.
Well, I have no doubt that you guys are gonna get back together, okay?
He's not gonna let you get away. He's way too smart to be stupid.
Let's hope so. Yes. Because I just want my husband back.
I want you to have that man back.
What's going on? You were gone this morning
when I got up. And when I didn't hear from you all
day, I just. I didn't want to steer away from
plants. I just kept packing.
So you taking dishes? Because I
thought you said you weren't taking anything outside the house except your clothes. Well,
I don't have to take the dishes, if that's a problem. No, no, babe,
it's cool. I mean, if you need them, take them. I'm just saying, whatever you
take, just let me know, because I'm gonna have Karina put most of the stuff
on ebay. So tired of hearing that name.
Why are you selling things on ebay?
Selling the house. This house?
Yeah. Why are you selling our house?
Peter made me an offer and asked if
I would take Wright's investments to Europe.
I said yes.
Wow. I leave next month.