Well, that. That's not the life I signed up for.
And by the way, romance novel used to be our life.
Stop. Wait. Where you going?
Well, you need to ask your father for a key
to the house. I did ask him. What did he say? I'm not responsible
enough. Noelle, you 16 years old?
Like, what are you doing over here that's making you so irresponsible?
I don't know. He just says it. Girl,
you better not be sneaking. No boys over there. What? I don't even date.
Well, I don't want to kick somebody butt. No. No boys.
But I will need your Social Security number. My Social Security?
Mm. To claim you on my taxes for all the food you eat and all
the wanting you. Hey, I'm a growing teenager. I have to eat.
Hey, Ms. Wright. Hey, sweetie. I got you some of those airplane books.
Sweet. Did you bring them? Of course. Hi.
So, have you recovered from your last night's episode?
Scandal. Ms. Washington.
What's this? I hope you don't fight me.
Are you serious? As a heart attack.