Malazine is getting cold.
Jihad. Yeah.
Turn to me.
What's up?
Are you happy?
Happy? What do you mean happy?
I mean, are you happy being married to me?
Most times, yeah. I'm very happy. Just perfect
for me. I just don't ever want us to get a divorce.
Well, that's not even on the table for discussion.
Good. You know I love you.
I know.
Carmen and Omar are divorcing.
What? Are you. Are you serious?
Stop playing. Come on now. You know I wouldn't play with something like that.
I was just over the house a few days ago. He did not mention that.
I did call him a couple of times a day. He didn't pick up dog.
Wait, Is that why you're asking if I'm happy? Mm.
You know, you my other half. Ain't nobody
else gonna love them dirty underwear. I don't have dirty underwear.
Wow. Sorry to hear that about Carmen and
Omar. That's crazy. Yeah, it's crazy. It's just a huge wake
Look at me.
I'm here, right? I ain't going nowhere.
You understand? Do you understand?
Yes. Right?
Give me some covers.
We go to people's weddings, we throw rice, we celebrate them.
And then where are we for them when it's time for them to talk about
getting a divorce? The hell are you talking about? You know what I'm talking about.
Carmen loves this man. I need you to talk to him today day. Okay?
Don't just okay me, Damon. I'm serious. Is that all right? Shut up and give
me a kiss while you go to work.
Yummy. Strawberries. I like it. You back in that house? Yeah.
Oh, girl, please. My back can't take it. If you love me like you say
you love me, go and get that door like you would Halle Berries.
I bet you I get that door better than I get halberries. I bet.
Get in the car, woman. Come on. Thank you. That's how I talk to Halle.
Grady, get in the car. Get in the car. Behind you. Just cause she light
skinned don't mean I won't tell her what to do. Come on, get in the
car. Have a good day. Okay. Go call him. I will. You promise?
I promise. Today? Today. Right now. Mm. You promise. Twice.
Twice. Twice. I got you, Stanji. You do me like that every day. All right.
Bye. By.
Wait, I didn't. I forgot. I need a ride
You know what? You just want to get some in the car,
Hey, how are you? How are you? Good to see you. Really? You passed
the handshakes Give me a hug, woman. Oh, okay. Wow.