I wasn't gonna let him kill me. I was just gonna let him bite me
a few times. Girl, what. What are we gonna do with you?
I thought that maybe if I got hurt, then you and
Ms. Wright would work out your marriage. Oh,
sweetheart. No, no, no, no, no. Listen, don't worry
about me and Mrs. Wright. I mean, I appreciate it, but we'll
work it out, okay? You're too smart and pretty. Be doing
stuff like that. Okay? Here comes my dad. Are you gonna tell him? No.
But you pull a stupid stunt like that again, I will. I think divorce
is stupid. Okay. Now I'm gonna tell him. Okay? Okay.
Sup, Mike? What's good?
Hey. Sup, baby girl? How you doing? Good. You all right?
Yes. Good, good, good. Hey, run over to the house. Let me highlight O real
quick. Okay. Bye, sweetheart. Hey, what's up, buddy?
What's good, man? You? You. How's work? It's work.
Yeah, you know, Listen, man, I want to thank you guys for everything y'
all done for my daughter, man. Hey, no worries. You know, Noelle's welcome over here
anytime. She's like family. Yeah, man, but you're doing a great job with her.
Well, you know, I'm trying, man. I'm trying. Hey, can I holler at you real
quick? Yeah. Listen, Noelle was
crying the other night. Yeah. And when I asked her what was wrong,
she said it was. Cause you guys was getting a divorce.
Yeah. Listen, bro, look, I know it's none of my business,
but if you can work that thing out, try to.
Don't make the mistake. I did. You know, y' all
are good people, man. Y' all good for each other,
so. Yeah, thanks. All right.
All right. Thank you. All right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Hey, my company gets those tickets for the Hawks here,
and we'll go check one out. That's what's up. Yeah. First round on me.
Let's go. All right. Let me hook up these noodles. Yeah. Yeah. I'll see you,