Hey. Hi. Come on in. Thank you,
Karina. Thank you.
Well, I whipped up some spicy teriyaki shrimp with sauteed
spinach and garlic dipped roasted red
skin potatoes. Mmm. And if
you have some room in your stomach for some dessert after that, I made my
grandmother's homemade recipe for her baked apple crumb pie with
in season Kelly green granny apples. Oh. Go ahead.
Voila. And you're welcome.
I do not know what to say. This, this, this looks
great, Karina. Thank you. You're welcome. Here you are.
Mm. And thank
you. So are you excited about the move yet?
Uh, yeah. Yeah, actually I am. Good.
Because I was thinking that I could take my two week vacay and I can
come out there and help you set up. Oh, okay. That's great. I mean,
so where would you be staying? With you.
Karina, my wife already thinks we're messing around,
but we're not.
Okay. You know what? Wow. It makes
me laugh that two good looking professionals who are of the opposite sex.
What? We can't work together without somebody thinking that we're sleeping together.
Relationships and marriage, I guess, are just something that I would never be
able to figure out. I don't know. Yeah. Makes two of us.
Yeah. Because I haven't. I haven't been in a relationship in
about three years. And when I was. I was actually supposed
to get married, but the week before my wedding, he tells me that he's been
hiding his newborn. Damn.
Yeah. So what'd you do? Everything.
I bounced back. Okay? I focused on me. I went to
school and got my master's. And look, now I'm working with you. And I am
really, really looking forward to Europe.
God, I love a woman with tenacity,
ambition. Thank you.
And I know what I want. And I want you to be successful.
Karina. I don't get it.
How are you single?
I gotta tell you, that guy who messed up,
he didn't see a good thing right in front of him. I know.
And neither does she.
You are so beautiful.
Thank you. And your wife is
really lucky because if I had somebody like that, I would never give him up.
Just.