Carmen. Ugh. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Carmen.
Is that why you did not fight for our marriage? Carmen? What are you talking
about? You're the one who wanted a divorce, not me. Is that really all you
have to say to me, Omar? Okay,
what are you even doing here? Why is she here?
You never know why I'm here.
You think I wanted this? I didn't want this.
They better be glad I was nowhere near. Their body parts would have been flying
everywhere. You know, we have been trying to have a baby forever,
and then this happens. This happens. Now,
I never even thought I would think this,
but I might consider just getting rid of it.
Okay, now you're just talking stupid. Jasmine. My plan was
never to have a baby by myself. No, no, no, no. You know, we don't
believe in abortions, okay? We got your back, all right? I mean,
hell, you can get a baby. My last name.
You guys have been trying to have a child for a long time.
Yep. This. I can't believe this
happened. This baby is a blessing.
I'm gonna be an auntie. At the end of the day, I'm gonna be an
auntie. And we gotta celebrate that. Girl. Where you put the glasses at? There's a
vodka in there. Well, you gonna have some milk?
It's okay, baby.
Yeah. So this is my home. So,
what'd you guys think? It's amazing. It is perfect.
And how about that bathroom? Great. And the closet?
Oh, already on it. Love it. I love to hear that. Patio,
too. It's perfect. I'm not sure if you guys have any kids. We have a
great school system, so. I mean, this house is great for
children. Oh, and the living room is going to be the perfect size for all
of them. Yeah. So hopefully we can do some business, Sell the house
rather quick because I got some business in Europe, so.
Yeah. But thank you. Nice to meet you. Thank you so much for the opportunity
to check it out. Thank you so much, Mr. Wright. Thanks for your time.
I really do appreciate it. Come on, Felicia. You know you're my girl. Thank you,
guys. Have a good day, okay? Thank you. You too.
Hey, excuse me. What are you doing? Well, I just came by
to. Wait, wait, wait. I know you're not about to sell the house, right?
Yeah, Samir, I'm about to sell the house. Don't act like you don't know what's
going on. Okay, look, I'm not in the mood to talk. I appreciate,
you know, you guys trying to. Okay, well, look, I just came over Cause I
need to talk to you about something. So. Talk to me about what? You know
what. Forget it. No, but. Bye. I'm not in the mood.