Oh, hey, Karina. Hey. I called you earlier.
I know. I'm sorry I couldn't take your call. But I know you wanted to
talk to me about something. What's up? Yeah, well, I heard from Peter
and he suggested that I take you to Europe as
my vp. Are you serious? Yeah. Are you serious? Oh, my God.
Are you serious? Yeah. Wow. Okay, first, don't look
at me. That I didn't have anything to do with this. No, I know.
I swear. I promise you. I promise. I believe you. Okay. So what did
you tell him? I told him that I would consider
it. So you're cons. You're considering taking me
to Europe as my vp?
Europe. Yay. Oh, my God. This is awesome. This is awesome.
Thank you. No, I mean, you will not regret this. I promise you. You and
me together in Europe. We're gonna make magic together.
Yeah. Take Europe by storm. Yes, we will. I mean,
think about it. Europe has a slew of untouched territory and it won't
take us long to launch. Cause think about it. All we have to do is
use the same formula that we use here, over there, and then by the time.
Hey. Okay. What's wrong?
Nothing else.
What? Okay. Does this have anything
to do with what happened, you know, that night?
Is.
Your wife? This is about your wife?
Yeah. Karina, I like
you a lot, but I love my wife.
And this between you and I,
it can't happen.
So, unfortunately, I'm gonna have to say no to Europe.
But I'm gonna tell Peter yes for you.
Yeah. I think you will be great in Europe. No, listen to me.
Just hear me. Just hear me. Just listen.
I think you can take Europe by storm and
set up your own brain, your own name. You're that good.
Yeah, that sounds great. That sounds
really great. So I'll talk to you
later? Yeah, sure. We can talk about the numbers tomorrow and all the logistical
stuff. You know how we do. Yeah. Street.
See you later. My type of street.
Sweet.