So, thank you for bringing me to lunch. No problem. I know this
is about more than lunch, because not often do you ask me
out in the middle of the week. That bozo, August,
he asked if I'd like to stay in his fare room until my place is
ready. And you said? Well, I told him
no. But the more I think about it, I should take him up on his
offer. Samara and I both have rooms that
you can stay in, so you're fine. I know, I know. But the thing is,
I don't want to impose on my best friends and your relationships just because mine
is in the can. Oh, ma', am, do you hear yourself? Cause you
sound crazy. You will stay with us. Oh, no. But you know what? If you
do stay with him, let me tell you how it's gonna go. Oh, you're gonna
get there. Y' all gonna cuddle. You gonna spoon with him a little bit.
Then you're gonna have sex with him. Then you're gonna become another notch on his
belt, and then, boom. He's gonna throw you out like an orange pill.
Carmen, you. You are slipping. Really, Jasmine?
That's a lot. What do you mean I'm slipping? You have completely
lost your mind. Do you hear yourself? That fool
should have not even had the audacity or the balls even to ask you.
Any mess like that. The Carmen that I know, love and admire
for the amazing woman that she is, would have told him off.
Very kind. Like, I just don't want to impose on you and Samira.
Plus, I don't have the money for a hotel right now. I mean, I'm giving
Omar everything. That's just as much your house as it is Omar's.
You sleep in the bed and put him on the couch. Did Omar
ask you to leave? No. Oh, good. Cause he know I'm crazy.
I'm sure Damon had told him a whole lot of stories about me.
I mean, but my marriage is practically over, right? I don't
see the problem in me taking that man up on his offer. Do you
hear the insanity that continues to spew out of your mouth? You have
lost your mind completely. Carmen. Inviting a third
party into a pending marriage is insane.
A few days. That's it. That's all it is. Just a few days.
Okay, you know what? This is simply disappointment. Because they say
disappointment triggers temporary insanity. And, honey,
you are acting out. You are completely irrational.
I just hate that Omar is coming out of this relationship and this
marriage without a scratch. Waiter. Come on.
Okay, this is all about Omar. You're doing this to get back at him.
I can eat now. I'm gonna need a dessert and a key lime pie to
go with my order. Where is the waiter?
Let me get this. Six fried chicken wings,
two coleslaws and a basket of fries.
And let me get a Diet Coke with that.