Hey.
Did you want a sandwich? No,
I just had lunch with the girls.
The papers are on the counter.
Yeah, I signed him.
Yeah, you did sign.
My place won't be ready until the end of the week, so I was wondering
if I could stay here on the couch until then.
What's up with the hotel?
Just forget I asked.
You know, it's. That attitude of yours is why we're here now.
Are you seriously telling me that I can't sleep here? I mean,
why did you even ask me? Out of respect. Omar.
Why are you so callous about everything? Everything like
what? Everything like everything. Christ,
Carmen. I signed the papers. What more do you want from me?
I'll just go to the hotel. Oh, yeah, there goes Carmen and acting like a
spoiled brat again. Spoiled brat?
I'm a spoiled brat. I am leaving this
marriage with nothing but my clothes. Now, this relationship has been in trouble
a long time, and you know that. No,
I didn't know that. Yeah, Carmen, we had problems,
but every married couple does. You were working on
a divorce right under my nose. And then you going clothes on a place.
Baby, you leaving me? So you really think I give a damn where you lay
your head at night?