Look, Carmen, I'm sorry.
You can stay here as long as you like. It's okay. I'll get a hotel
room until my place is ready. No, just stay.
No. I don't want you to have to do me any favors. I'm not.
But I'll sleep better knowing that you're safe.
Omar. Yeah?
What happened to us?
Jesus, Carmen. I don't know. I mean,
I guess couples just grow out of love.
I guess. I don't know.
Sweet.
Car. Car. Sit up.
I made you some tea. Thank you, baby, but you need
to go away before you get sick.
You sick? I'm sick. Thank you.
Everything okay?
They got me jumping through these unnecessary hoops for my broker's license that they don't
have everyone else jumping through. It's like I
just wanna say, forget it. I don't.
You can do unnecessary hoops in your sleep. Be smart like that.
Be with the man like that.
You see? That's one of the billions of reasons why I married you. Yes.
I can't wait to tell Jasmine and Samira. A billion. I'll beat you,
man. They can't hold a candle to us. A candle or the moon or
the sun. Do you believe in me? Yeah,
baby. All day, every day.
Sunday. Yeah. I mean, in a
minute. Sit out here and take it all in.
Sam.
Uh, hey, I. Morning. I made some extra breakfast.
A little too much, probably force of habit. But I can make you a plate
if you like. No, it's okay. I have a breakfast meeting with Karina, which I'm
already late for. But I'll take you up on your Waffle House smelling breakfast next
time. Okay. Have a going. You too.
So, thanks for signing the rest of the papers. Should have you squared away in
a few days. Oh, finally. Thank you. Yeah. But thank
you for this breakfast. It is absolutely delicious. You're welcome.