I thought Tee was one of the
best rappers there was in
believe
that?
I mean, he-- Not exactly ugly,
but you know, if we could keep
the brothers.
All right, look, y'all, stop.
Stop, it's funny, y'all got me.
told us to get whatever we could
get.
Girl, that's a trophy. What is
this? That's the money that
No cash?
Okay, I don't know. This
sandwich looks good. And I'm
It's not a medallion. Mm-hm?
That's a IUD. Women put that in
Listen, look, that's all fun and
games. Y'all got to the count of
of this is my money.
That's your money? This
is my money.
Okay, sidebar. What's that? Get
over here. Oh, right, sidebar.
Any money that comes in this
house? Yeah. Is your money. Any
Excuse me, caramel. I'm gonna
need to get the rest of that
I'm sorry, JoJo, but this is my
money.
Okay, now look, she's trying to
embarrass you in front of
Just like that. Okay. Um, hey, I
said give me the money, bitch.
Call me out of my name again.
Say it again. To her face. Say
it again. Okay. Oh, you must
it. Did I
do good? Oh,
Jesus.
Okay.