So you are the agency that Clarion hired to clean up his image.
Wow. Guilty as charged.
You know what's worse about it is that Adam didn't think there was
anything wrong with us representing them. And you do?
No, I dropped the account this morning. I called them.
So how they take that? They asked me for Adam's number.
Don't tell me they told you that you're done in this town. Yeah. Well,
guess what. I'm not worried. I did it once, I will do
it again. Only this time on my own.
Look at you, Marcy Chandler.
Jewel. I'm proud of you.
Wow. It took me blowing the biggest
opportunity of my life to get you to squeeze those words out.
Don't start. You're so dramatic.
Found some more candy canes. Oh, good. Perfect. Put some over there.
Okay. Oh, my God. Remember when we were little and we used to try to
go to bed before the sun went down? Oh, my God, yes.
Terrified that if Santa caught us, he would put sawdust in
our eyes. What was that? That's kind of cool of Santa, don't you think?
tomorrow's Christmas. Yeah, tomorrow's Christmas.
And then the next day you
leave. For five years.
Dana, I'm really sorry that we lost touch.
For the record, for what it's worth, you have always been
my favorite cousin and my best friend. I know.
I know. Why else would you leave New York
in the middle of a huge campaign just to come spend one last Christmas,
you know? Good point. Good point.
I had an interesting chat with Blair today.
How'd that happen? Well, we bumped into each other at
the cemetery. Okay,
okay, okay. Your crazy husband, Frankie, he's always
had this notion that Blair has a crush on me. I don't know.
What do you think? Well, what would you do if it were true?
Woman, I'm asking you a question. Just. Can you answer it, please? Well, why don't
you ask him tomorrow at dinner? You know what?
Maybe I will. Good.
I miss you. I'm gonna miss
you too.