Honey, I made you hot chocolate with marshmallows. Thank you,
mama. Thank you. Cookies. There you go.
And guess what I made em.
Look at the miniatures in there. You okay, honey?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You know, Adam and I had a run in with Blair at
church. Huh. Really? What kind of run in?
Dude's crazy again. What kind of
run in? Yeah, no, I don't. I really don't think it was that important.
Just. Is everything okay with Blair?
It's tough for him this time of year, honey.
Yeah. Especially with Cruella being on his heels, and then he's
got that big Clarion lawsuit, so. Clarion candy? Yeah.
Yeah. You probably heard him. Yeah, but what does Blair have to do with Clarion
candy? What lawsuit? Oh, man, you name it. Just unfair
labor practices. What? Sex, race, gender,
age discrimination? Yeah, one of Blair's clients got fired
because she blew the whistle on him. And, you know, Preston represents him. He's been
doing a pretty good job so far keeping things up under wraps, but, man,
he's got a lot of work ahead of him if he wants to clean up
the image. Mm. Good luck with that. Tell me about it.
I'll be right back. I'm gonna see you later. Oh. You okay?
What is going on? What's wrong with her?