It's getting cold out here, Frank. Yeah, it is getting chilly. Man, that hawk coming
in early this year. Hey dawg,
tell me something. Do you really think that three of those prissy
little Chandler women can haul in a 10 foot tree by theyself? No,
but it'll definitely be fun watching them try. Man, you right about that.
Look, man, I gotta get out of here, man. Are you back on the case?
Huh? Man, you know it, man, and it is driving me crazy. What's going on
with it, man? The client, she having second thoughts now, man. Cause nobody in the
company want to back up her story. You know what I'm saying? They all afraid,
man. Must be lonely being a whistleblower. Man,
who you telling? Hey, listen, I know we done talked about this a
million times before, but I gotta ask again. Something about you
and Charlene, man. Man, we good? We good.
Liar. Come on, man, listen, you know I think
that you deserve better, okay? And all Charlene is gonna do is just suck
you dry before she robs you. Look, man, everybody can't have
the perfect mate like you and Marcy. So just let it go. Oh,
wait a minute, hold on. Kinda sounds like to me jealous
of Marcy's new man. I don't know. Jealous of Marcy?
Yeah. Dude, did you fall down and hit your head? It's me
we talking about, man. Marcy. I know,
man. Look, man, look, whatever. I'll see you at the tree farm later on,
all right? All right, cool, man. I'll let you later. Always on
that Marcy stuff. Man, you tripping. I know, Sounds crazy, right? You jealous?
Hey,