I done felt every single emotion that you feeling right now.
So you gotta believe me when I tell you that you. You gotta leave that
in the past. Cause if you don't, you ain't ever gonna
be able to move forward.
You gotta be able to forgive, brother.
Forgive Donnie? What, I look like forgiving him?
Get off of me. I ain't forgetting you. You don't deserve
my forgiveness. Everything I worked for, I did it alone,
Kim. But, Donnie, whose fault was it that you were alone?
You left us. We were here,
Leah. You ain't got nothing to do with this. Well, it feels like I have
a lot to do with this.
I only came here because Mama Rose told me that
she was sick. She told me my son was sick.
Stop calling me your son. That's number one.
And that's my business. That's my business,
okay? Mama Rose,
I'm sick. The doctors gave me
a few weeks, two weeks ago.