Well, you know, I know that is usually a tradition for us to open up
just one gift on Christmas Eve, but we're going to do that a little later.
Well, actually, I have one for my dinny. For me?
For you. Open it up. What is
this? It was last minute, so I hope you like it.
You hate it, don't you? I know you might be a little too
old for it. I just thought. Mama Rose, but I
love it, Mama Rose. I love it.
It's very. Nostalgic.
That's the word I was looking for. Nostalgia.
Thank you so much. You're welcome.
That's cool.
All right. Bye,
everybody. Bye. Take care. Hey,
y'. All, Excuse me. Hey, hold on, hold on real quick.
Where you going? I only came because I promised Mama
Rosa. Okay. Why you rushing, though? Leon wants to say something.
Of course. You know what? I think you should
stay just a little bit longer. We like it. I mean, I'd like
You know, I think I really have to be honest with myself.
Okay.
When you left, you didn't even think about me. You didn't even care.
You didn't call, you didn't check in, you didn't even keep in touch.
And look, Donnie, it's been about 10 years.
This is the first time I'm even seeing you or hearing your voice.
And I get it. I have moved on with Leon.
Although things aren't perfect. This is crazy.