Everything okay? Just the
situation here with these European people. Want to merge or something?
If there was an award for the world's busiest man, you'd definitely be a contender.
All the bills are paid, right? Mm.
Bills are paid.
What's so funny? Does Karina.
You know. Do we get this joke about those cats in Europe and how they
talk and how they act? It's. It's crazy. It's still. Inside joke.
Inside joke? Yeah,
You. Would you like me to make your lunch to go,
or. Nah, babe, I'm good. I'm good.
Good. Damn,
these European cuts are so hard to get on.
Karina said that they make you look more powerful
in a business meeting. Karina is a fashionista
too. All right. Love you.
What's up, cole?
Hey, you. Hey. Hey. I got your email.
Okay. And I gotta be honest.
Carlos is gonna say this is just decent. Decent?
Well, why just decent? Because the numbers
are too conservative for the Latin market. Too conservative? Yes.
Come on, Omar. You know you can do these numbers in your sleep.
Think so? I know so. And I know you can do better.
Hold on. I gotta make this call. Okay.
Hey. Hey. I got your text about dinner.
Uh, yeah, babe, whatever you wanna make. I'm. I'm. I'm easy.
I don't have a, you know, preference. Okay. Sure, sure. Also,
while I have you on the phone, I wanted to ask if it's okay that
we can RSVP for that gal I was telling you about. Uh, the gala.
The gala. That's the 12th, right? Yeah, the gala
I told you about a couple times. Um,
so, yeah, the 12th. 12th? Babe, we are.
This merger. We are so busy right now that I will not be able to
make that. Just the numbers. There's a lot going on,
so I think that. Look, I gotta get this phone call.
Rosensweg. He's calling in from New York, and I gotta close this deal, so let
me call you back. Okay? All right. All right,