Mom's making some more hot cocoa if you want to come.
Hard to believe tomorrow's Christmas Eve.
Did you know?
Had no idea.
I mean, I figured there had to be a reason why they wanted to
do a complete image makeover, but I didn't know it was this Scott's
You know, honestly, Marcy, I don't see
what difference it makes. There are clients.
They hired us to do a campaign. That's what we're doing. We did not do
any of these things to those people. This is business. This happens every day.
Look, just don't tell me this is gonna affect the way you do business with
them. No, it's definitely not gonna affect the way I do business with them because
I'm not going to do business with them. Are you kidding me right
now? Do I look like I'm kidding you right now? After weeks
of working on this account, all the long hours, countless phone calls, you dragged
me all the way out here to Challenge town? I am currently pretending to be
your fiance right now. All this for
this account? And you wanna throw it all away because your childhood crush is representing
some chick that's got beef with a candy cane? He's not my childhood crush.
Well, really? Really? Where's your
focus? Is that all you can say right now? No, it's not all I can
say. All I can say is I'm not gonna allow myself to be used to
clean up somebody else's dirt. You heard what Frankie said. These people are slimy.
How do you even know that's true? Because I know it's true. Cause Blair said
so. You really think we should continue
to work with these people? I honestly think we should continue to work with
them. I honestly think I busted my butt on this case. And I honestly
think you owe me. I. What? Yeah, you owe me.
You think I owe. Listen. All right? You owe me. I think Blair was right
about you. And you're right. I owe you. I do owe you. I owe you
a flight back to Chicago. And I got
you on that. I also got your Christmas bonus. Marcy. Tonight. Nope.
Fully paid. Sir, for all your services rendered. Don't worry.
I'll take care of you tonight. Okay, Marcia. Okay. No, no, no. Window, aisle.
Let me know. I'm booking your flight tonight. Relax.
Calm down. Cause you are about to make a huge
mistake. No, Adam, I already made a huge mistake.
I hired you, see, because people were telling me about you,
how unscrupulous you were, and I didn't listen. I was
so. I was so wanting to win that I didn't listen.
So now what? You don't want to win anymore?
You want to keep doing all these little penny pinching accounts like you've been doing
all these years?
No. See, I'm going to win. I'm going to win.
That's what I do. Jewel Advertising
will be a huge success because of me. Not because of you.