My bad. It's okay. I understand.
I know that checking in comes into territory once you're married, so I
totally get her. Of course you do. Cause you girls stick
together. That's right. Girl power.
That's sweet, though. What's that? You know, checking in.
You love your wife? Yeah, I love
my wife. I mean, yeah. I mean, I've known my wife since we were
in the fourth grade. I mean, we weren't married that long. I mean,
but yeah, I mean, we have our ups and downs, but I love my wife
a lot. Wait a minute.
What's going on in that head? Ms. Karina?
Okay. I said okay. I. I believe
you. Okay, well, I believe I need to make a phone call
to Rosenzweig in New York. So get back to work. You know what? Fine.
Cause I got a client to call, too. You ain't the only one, okay?
Cause money calls. I know, Miss Money. Go make that
money then. That's right. Mm. You know what? Whatever. I'm coming back
here in 15 minutes when I'm done. I bet you are. 15. Yeah. Yeah.
Greg Rosewag. Omar. Right here.
Hey, Ms. Ray. Hey, sweetie. Thank you. Dad isn't home
yet? No, he's still at work.
Oh, Ms. Wright, did I tell you I'm in the summer aviation program?
Aviation program? Mm. Okay, so you
wanna fly planes? Well, I wanna start off as a pilot, then one day on
my own airline. Aw, Noel, that's amazing. Keep your head right where it's
at. You got my class next year. Mm. Third period.
You know, Ms. Wright, I could have jumped that fence and went through the window,
but I was so hungry. Thank you so much for this meal. You're welcome,
sweetie. But isn't that crazy dog over in the next yard? Yes, ma'.
Am. Noel, don't you ever jump that fence.
I cannot run that dog. No, you can't. That dog has four legs.
You only have two. Yes, ma'. Am. Oh, hey, Mr. Wright.
Hey. What's up, Noelle? Hey, your father's outside in the front for you. Oh,
okay. Well, thank you, Ms. Wright. You're very welcome.
See you later, girl. She's a good kid.
I mean, she seems trustworthy. I don't know why her father just doesn't give her
keys to the house. He's a man. Sometimes men do stupid things.