I know you don't believe this, but when they told me
that you were in trouble, I didn't think twice.
Okay? This is what a father's supposed to do.
I'm trying.
Regardless of what reasons I abandoned you,
I didn't do right by you and Darius. And I know that doesn't
matter what reasons I had.
What were your reasons?
Truth is, before your mama died, I had a bad gambling
problem. And when she passed, it got worse.
And a lot of people didn't want to see me alive.
I was worth more to them dead than walking around on them. A dead.
So I figured you and your brother be safe with your mama Rose.
You know what?
Be honest with you. I could use
that as an excuse. But the real reason was. Was because I was a coward.
I was scared of raising you and your brother by myself.
Couldn't see myself doing that without your mama.
She was my rock. I didn't think I could do it then.
Your mama Rose was doing such a good job with both of you.
Donnie. I didn't want to mess that up.
You my father, man, would have been happy if
you just played ball with us, took us for a ride around town. Man,
I just wanted you present,
that's all.
For what accounts, Donnie? I'm here now.
I'm present. I'm here by your side.
And I promise you, I ain't going nowhere. And with everything I got left
in me, I'm gonna be here for you
and your brother.
Can you just let
go of all this anger and just find it in your heart to forgive me?
You ain't gotta say it.
Just take my hand, son.