It's all itemized. If you guys look at line 29, you'll see
how much you made off your investments in the 770 accounts. If you guys
have any questions, email me. No, no, we good. We good.
Thank you. Thank you. First of all, thank you for giving us the opportunity to
invest in your, you know, your urban development program. Thanks, bro. Yeah, yeah,
that's cool. But you good?
Yeah, I'm cool. You sure, man?
Okay. It's Carmen. Like, she's been tripping
lately, man. Like, the other night, she dropped my phone on a glass of water.
That ain't tripping, man. That's crazy. She's just been, like, complaining and nagging,
trying to bait me in arguments. I don't know,
guys. I'm just getting sick of it. Getting sick of it. All right,
look, if you want an outside opinion on your marriage and you ready to,
you know, listen and you can handle it,
let me know. Are you Dr. Phil now? No,
no, I'm not Dr. Phil. I'm just saying, look,
honestly, no disrespect, right? When we go out as couples,
Jasmine, you know, she all on my lap. Samira, she all on
his shoulder. You know, you and Carmen, you on one side of the room,
she on the other. For real. It's like the other night, like game night.
Y' all look like y' all was about to have a boxing match or something.
I'm telling you. Look, look, look. Whatever, man. Look, that's your wife, right?
All she wants is affection. That's it. How you think
she feels? She see us with our wives and you over there in the corner
on your phone. On that phone, man. Okay, now you're just making stuff up.
I'm making it up? Oh, I'm trying to holler at you from a
place of love, right? When last time you tapped that? Dude, that's disrespectful,
man. What, D. You ain't got no chill? So disrespectful. What? Dude, why y' all
up in the man's bedroom? I'm just saying. Look, I remember her, like, walking around,
right? She had to, like, she looked like she was full of life. She had
a glow. She had this light about her. Now she got a sad face all
the time, like she, you know, mean, mugging us and stuff. Look, enough about my
wife, all right? Sorry I even brought it up. Look, I'm just saying. That's your
wife, right? She's a woman. She needs attention. You know? She's like a little flower.
You gotta water it. Show it. Attention, love and affection. She wants that
from her husband. Look, I'm telling you, you better do that. Cause there's a lot
of thirsty dudes out there in the streets. They can see her coming from 100
miles away. Whatever. It's whatever.