Hey, look, I'm gonna sit down and play cards with you, but you don't have
to take that down a notch. Listen, he's like that all the time.
Is he really? Yes. Hey, don't be mad because I don't learn how
to turn my anger into a positive motivation.
What book you read that out of? If you must know,
it's a book by Gary Chapman called Anger Taming
a Positive Emotion.
Positive. What's so funny? Oh, man, I just ain't
never heard you talk like that. I ain't used to it. It sound funny.
Well, what are you used to, Donald?
Because I ain't seen you in years.
Matter of fact, I'm surprised you don't
even remember what I look like. Listen, man, just calm down.
I'm just used to used to you being aggressive, that's all.
Trust and believe, brother. It's still in there.
These days, I just try to be more happy.
And ain't nothing wrong with that. Hey, yo, Donnie,
man, tell me this, bro. What's so good about Atlanta?
Can't be that good unless you
found a woman. Well, I ain't found a woman. Not you.
Oh, so, wait, wait. So. So. So you in the men?
I mean, look, don't. Don't get me wrong, because we ain't judging, right?
Matter of fact, Matt broke the ice with that when he married Kenny.
Yeah, I told him that already. Look, I ain't in the. Man,
I'm into my job. That's basically all I do.
Oh, but you work for that book firm,
right? It's a literary agency. Well, well, yeah, yeah,
that. But literary agents make good. They make good money. Yeah.
Reasonable pay. We good. Reasonable. Cause you
got a black card, and a real black card at that. Only black card
I ever seen is a cash app card.
Yeah, I can tell he got money.
I can look at how you're dressing and tell you got money.
People with money think it's cool to dress like that.