It's a four door silver Infinity. How hard is that to find?
And it better not be one scrap on my car. You understand me?
Nothing. Missing out. What?
You arrived here in an Uber. Your car.
It's not here in an Uber.
Well, why didn't you tell me that then, man? That's what I've been trying to
tell you the whole time. So unprofessional. I know.
Oh, get him. I'm sick of this, man. I'm about to quit.
I'm about to quit. This is irritating,
Man. Did you have to spray that? Hey. Yes. Man, you funky as hell,
bro. I'm funky? Yes.
I ain't got time to stop at home. Look, how far are
we? It's right around the corner up here. Tell you what, do me a favor,
just. Just stop right now. Right here? Yeah. Stop right now. Gotcha.
Donald. Well, hello, Cheyenne. Good to see you. Good to see you.
Looking beautiful as always, by the way. Stop it. I took the liberty of ordering
you a drink as well, if you don't mind. No, it's all good. Thank you.
Good. Thank you. Let's get down to business. So we
have sort of an issue. An issue? What kind of issue?
Well, you know the publishing company, My first book was with Norman
and Company. I'm fully aware. Yep. Okay. Well,
in the contract it states that they have first rights of refusal
to any content that I have. Okay. So my guess
is they're trying to sue you. Yes, but by this
document, my current book is a derivative of my
last book. Okay, has your counsel,
has he reviewed this yet? Of course.
And he says that if they take us to court,
there's a possibility they could win.
Yeah.
What do I do? How can I fix this?