Hey, Noelle. How's that fall program going? It's good.
Here's your mail. Thank you.
What's going on? Why you sitting out here looking all
sad? Is it true? It's not true
you and Mr. Wright are getting a divorce?
I wasn't eavesdropping. I just heard you guys talking
when I was coming up from the basement.
So is it true?
Yeah, it's true. But why?
I guess sometimes people just fall out of being in love.
Like my dad and Ms. Lewis. I don't know what's going on
with your dad and Ms. Lewis. They had this big argument about
my dad loving my mom. But I don't understand.
I understand. See, it's probably a lot more than
just about your dad loving your mom.
Love and being in love, two totally different things as grown folks.
So wait, your dad's dating Ms.
Lewis? Yeah. So why don't you just sometimes go down to her
place when you're locked out? She's only a few doors down. Because I
like being around you and Mr. Wright. It's fun being in
a two parent household. And I
know you guys don't have the perfect marriage, but I see how you
guys look at each other. Ms. Wright. And this love.
But why? Don't marriages ever work out? No.
Come here. Look at me. Now, look, I know your parents had a divorce.
And I know that Mr. Wright and I are going through a divorce. But there
are plenty of marriages out there that work. It's just that both parties
have to be willing to work at it. You understand? Yeah,
that's right. Yes, ma'. Am. Mr.
Wright is a good person and he teaches me a lot about life.
Can you please just take him back and show me that marriages work?
Come here.