Right, sir. How you doing, man? I'm good. Good,
good, good. I had to drop some papers off. I hope that's okay with you.
Okay. Yeah, it's cool. How you
doing? I'm good, I'm good. I'm good. It's amazing what you guys did to the
house, man. It's absolutely beautiful. Yeah, well, you know, we got taste.
We're not slobs. Well, I guess I'll be going now. That's right.
Think about that offer. Okay? I will. And I thank you for your time.
Thank you, Mr. Wright. Always a pleasure, sir. Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. You guys have a good one. Okay. You know what? Let me get
the door for you. Excuse me, honey.
All right, brother? Quite, sir. Yeah, have a good one.
You as well. Really?
See, that's what I'm talking about. Yo, that pisses me off, man.
I'm telling you. I hate that snake dudes, right? Just chilling in
the cut, lurking. Do you not care that your wife could be cheating on you?
D, I know my wife better than you, all right? Just remember that. No,
I'm just saying. Why am I more pissed off than you? Just saying? No.
Cause you always overreact. What? No, you overreact. I'm going to my lawyer today,
getting those divorce papers, giving her Carmen and whatever makes her happy.
Who is she, man? Boom. Yo, that's what I'm
saying. Who's who? Who's who? Who. Who? What are you,
owl. Who is she or who's
he? Shut up. I mean, this is Atlanta. No, you so stupid.
All right, well, if you're referring to Karina, she's just a friend, a colleague,
someone who I work with. But you say she just a friend. Now the
truth comes out. Yeah, yeah, you see it. Okay, listen, for the record, I haven't
slept with her, okay? All right? No, if I. If I did, I would have
told you. Look, see, all this time, we thinking it's her and it's this dude.
Mm. Well, she is bad. Yeah, but, you know, when me and
Carmen got married, I was about my baby, man. You know, it was like that
for my parents. I thought it was gonna be like that for me. Okay,
so after the divorce, you gonna hit? Man, I don't know. God,
what is wrong with this guy? No, listen. Since I've
been married, Carmen's all I've ever known, okay?
I don't know. Maybe you guys are right. Maybe it's time to start looking towards
new things. Have you guys ever
cheated? You know, I thought about it. Had this
little honey dip at work, man. It was fine, too. But I
had to nip that. Nip that in the bud.