Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, no,
we are back. We are back. Yeah. No, this is a foolproof plan.
Yeah, the funny thing is her aunt helped me realize it.
See, her company's about to explode and as her husband.
You following me? Yeah.
Oh, you know me. Promise him anything. Work out the details later.
Uh huh. All I gotta do is seal the deal. You know
me. I can close. There you are. Uh huh.
Okay. Yeah. Red headphones. All right. Love you too,
Mom. Bye. Well, I just signed off
on the revisions to the comp, so they are on their way to the client
as we speak. Awesome. Yeah. You know, Adam, I certainly
couldn't have pulled off this account without you. I'm glad your agency flopped.
Blessing in disguise, I guess. Cause without that,
I wouldn't have gotten to work so closely with you. And I kind of
like this ring too. It's. Well, we're about to go fetch this Christmas tree,
so. Adam, you coming? Do I have a choice? No.
Come on, man. Excuse me. Okay. Bye. Bye. Have fun.
Get a good one.
See something.