What was that? What are you talking about? I'm over
there hugging all up on old boy. That's just an old friend.
You know that.
Ladies, slow down. Aren't you ready to go?
I mean, we kind of just got here.
This ain't my vibe. After I finish eating,
we're leaving.
Speak for yourself.
His trouble in parad. Guys, I told you he is no
good for her. I told you, Jean, stay out of them young folks.
Business no good. Where's Donald?
I don't know. I hadn't seen him in a while. Go check over here.
Take my bow with you.
Hey, Dr. Vero. Hey. I'm taking the medicine like you
told me to, but it just seems like it's not working.
I mean, I. I know you told me to enjoy my family and everything for
the holidays, but how can I when my. My stomach is hurting and I'm.
I'm feeling faint. Listen, I'm gonna need a
stronger prescription or something. This. It ain't working.
Whenever you can, give me a call back, please.
Thanks.
Everything okay? Yes, ma'. Am. Yes, ma', am. Everything is fine. I'll be downstairs
in a minute, all right? All right.