Do you like me? I like you.
I always have.
See, I know I told. This was so dumb.
No, no, no, no, it's not. It's not. Look, I'm laughing because I've been waiting
25 years to hear you say this. And was dumbass.
I didn't say it to you first. Are you serious?
I always thought you hated me. No, I didn't hate
you. I was. I was mad at you cause you didn't like me.
Shh. I can't hear anything. Well, I can't either with you talking. Well,
I can hear. Now. You two be quiet. You two be quiet. Shh. And where's
the rest of your dress? Myra used it to make that jacket. Shut up,
girl. And then
when you went away, I got angrier. I was mad at myself,
you, everybody. Wow,
Wally, you wanna hear something funny?
Even funnier than what I just said? I'm pretty sure I can top that.
Okay, go ahead. You're the reason why I never got married.
Okay. Yeah, you topped it, right? I mean, every guy I
ever dated was either just too.
Not good enough, not successful enough,
not you enough,