Not even married yet and you're already sneaking around. You rascal.
Hey, Aunt Myra. How are
you? Not everyone left. Oh, no. This time of year, we're all here.
24. Seven sisters are upstairs, and the boys went Christmas tree
hunting. Still?
Mm. Long as you hate to go to Walmart and get a Christmas tree.
Wow, you don't know, do you?
I guess Marcy hasn't told you about the great Christmas tree hunt she
started. We Chandler women, we don't do fake Christmas trees. Ain't nothing
like the real thing, baby. Ten footers. Fresh from the tree farm.
Ten foot tree? Mm. You know, Adam,
we're all very happy for you and Marcy.
Oh, yeah? I hadn't noticed. Mom's been waiting for this for
a long time. And actually, the whole family's been. To get married.
And having babies, that's always been a big deal to us.
You know, some families, it's all about maybe money,
education or sports. But for us, it's family tradition.
I never had a big family. It's always been just me and my mom.
Well, honey, you're about to have a slew of uncles and aunts
and cousins now that you and Ms. Marcy are gonna get hitched.
And you know, you couldn't be marrying into a better family than
the Chandler family. And with Marcy having her own business, baby,
you don't have to worry about her marrying you for your money. Mm.
You know, I have to be honest with you, Aunt Myra.
I work for Marcy's company. She's my boss.
Oh, okay. Well, not for long.
The two of you, you're gonna be partners in life. And I would imagine you'd
be business partners too. Really?
Mm.
You think so? I. Oh, absolutely. You know,
Marcy would just love having a partner to help her run that business.
And who better than her husband?
Who better? Once she starts popping out all
those babies, she won't
even be worried about that business. That will be the farthest thing from her mind.
Yeah. Mm. Hmm. Yeah.
Well, it's been great talking to you, Aunt Myra. Good talking to you,
too. Enlightening.
Have a good night. You too. Nephew. To be.