Negro, please. Right, right. I had to nip
it in the bud. You bit her in the butt is what you did.
Don't act like you wasn't. Stop playing, man. I'm gonna tell you the truth.
Tell you the truth, I think about it all the time. Hell, yeah, Plenty times,
man. Matter of fact, on the way over here, right, you know, was driving,
I seen two little shorties across the street looking like Laverne and Shirley, eyes like,
boom. Immediately thought popped into my head, right?
And see, that's what I do. I let my thoughts play out for a very
long time. See, I ain't never physically cheated, but in my mind,
I'm a ho. Yeah. Yes. And for that very reason, I know I'm going to
hell. Yeah, absolutely. See, me and the devil, you know, we on first name basis,
you know what I'm saying? I got my cell phone. Hold up. I think he
texted me right now. Hold on. Let me see.
Yes, Lucifer, Yes. What is wrong with you,
man? Nah, I'm playing. Yo, I understand what
you're saying, man. I love my wife, too, but it's hard, you know what I'm
saying? How you gonna not think about it at least? Well, karma's my
first love, and I thought she'd be my last. Like, I've been a loyal husband,
okay? Like when we went to the altar and we were saying our vows,
man, I meant it. I meant it at that time. We all do. Don't you
ever say no? I did. I know. Then, yeah, I did, too. And I still
do. And I think she did, too. But now it doesn't matter. So if anyone's
cheating, it's probably me. I cheated. Carmenada being number one, man, your wife should
not have to compete with anyone or anything. So focused
on my business, I lost sight of what's important. You know what's crazy? Carmen helped
me start the business. I messed up, fellas.
What about counseling? I mean, you guys ever thought about that?
Nah, I think it's too late for that, man. She don't want nothing to do
with me. Plus, those counselors, they don't know. They don't know you. They don't know
what they talking about. I wish I could just go back to the beginning and
start over. Not having karma by my side, man, I feel like I'm out of
business. Yeah,
so. So next week, after the divorce, you still
gonna hit, man? Shut up, Damon. What is.
I can't with you. I can't. I'm just trying to live.
Can our brother live?