Okay. How well do you know Adam?
What? This is about your fiance taking advantage of you.
Really? Now, hear me out.
I heard Adam upstairs on the phone. He was talking to some guy.
They were talking about how. Listen, just listen. They were talking
about taking over your company. He said that you two were
gonna become partners in more than one way. Yeah, okay,
listen, Mr. Big Town, small Town Lawyer, whatever,
Don't interrogate me, okay? I'm pretty sure you don't even know what you're talking about.
He's using you. He's trying to get ahead at your
expense. You don't know what you're saying. I know what I heard.
Just cut it out. You heard wrong. Hey, you okay? Ask him.
Ask him what?
Blair seems to think that you're using me to get your hands on my
You know, I always knew you didn't like me. Come on, man. You. No,
seriously. Ever since I got here, you've been trying to embarrass me in front of
Marcy and in front of her family. And now this is what you got,
right? Okay, so what did you mean when you said you two are gonna become
more than partners? Yeah, I heard your little conversation up there. You heard
my phone call up there? Yeah. Who are you?
You know, I don't know if you realize this, but Marcy and I are about
to get married. We're gonna be partners in life.
I know you got this little schoolboy crush on Marcy. It's real cute.
But you need to let that go. You know, unlike you and everybody else
in this town actually believe in Marcy. And I support everything that she does,
100%. I stand behind her. I bet you do.
Yeah, I do. I'm a lucky man. I'm a
very lucky man. I mean that, Marcy. You hear me?
I'm very lucky to have found you, and I'm
just now starting to realize that. Seriously? You buying this?
Marcy? I know you think you're, like, looking out for me or some kind.
I don't even know what you're. Marcy. Marcy. I don't even know who you are.
Because the Marcy I knew would have seen this clown coming
to Mile Away. Hey, man, that's enough, all right? We're at church. A guilty man
always strike first. Cut it out.