That. Wow.
Look, I'm sorry. I really don't mean for things to be that harsh. It's just
that you go back to Atlanta tomorrow and I'm left here still
continuing my life. I don't think I should disrupt that.
My God, this lady. What? No, no,
no. You good? Keep talking. I'm listening. Go ahead. I've already said everything.
Hold on one second. Let me answer this. Ms.
Rhymes. Hi, Donald. Hey. So I
was able to work out a deal with Norman and Company. Dana offered me numbers
that. Let's just say I'm happy. Very happy.
However, there's no need for a middleman, and so I'm relieving
you of your duties. Wait, what do you mean, you relieving me? We had
an agreement, Donald. There's nothing else to talk about.
Yes, and my lawyer carefully viewed this
agreement. There's some things we aren't too happy
with. Wait, wait. Hold on. Hold on. I can fix this. Let me
fix this. Okay, Donnie, you can't fix this. You lived your life, and now I'm
living mine. Frankly, Donald, there's nothing you can do.
I have already contacted Mr. Calhoun, informed him of my
Excuse me. I need to speak to my son.
He's all yours. Thank you.
Donnie, I need to talk to you, son.
Oh, son. Are you crazy?
I know you don't care for me much right now,
but this is important. I need to talk to you.
Back up. So you want to talk now?
You want to talk, huh? Like. Like, like, like, like you Father
of the Year now, right? Like. Like, like. Like you deserve any
of my time so I can indulge in. In what you want or what you
need. You lost?
I'm trying to talk to you. I've been trying to
talk to you. Many times I've tried to talk to you,
but I couldn't muster up the courage to face you.
Does that make you happy? Does it make you feel good? Then I
was embarrassed. I was ashamed. I was humiliated.
The guilt's been eating me up for years.