How's everything? I'm good, thank you. Good, good, good. Would you
like something to drink? Can I get you anything? No, I'm good.
All right. I got some bad
news. Have a seat.
Okay. Don't bite. And I got
some bad news. Okay, so which one you want first?
I guess I'll take the bad news. It's right underneath the bad,
bad news, so. It's amazing what you guys
did to this place. It's beautiful. Thank you. It's beautiful.
Well, let me get these papers. Listen, this is the dilemma.
The bank is holding things up because with your name being
on this house with your husband and doing a few of the other properties,
and now you're doing this by yourself. It's kind of like,
I got you. I got you. I'm gonna take care of you. Okay?
Okay. Remember when I first sold you guys this house?
Listen, I really just wanted to
say. Mm. I'm sorry to hear about the divorce. Thank you.
Thank you. But you know what they say, right? One man's
trash is another man's treasure. I'm pretty sure you won't have no problems finding
you a good guy. Did you just call me tranche? I did not.
I think I heard you say trash. I did not call you trash. I didn't
mean it like that. It's okay. Thank you. You're welcome. Here you go. All right,
so what am I supposed to do with all these papers?
Just take them to your attorney and let them look over them, and then you
can bring it to our lunch date. Our lunch date? Yeah. Our lunch date.
Yeah. Well, depending on how bad this other news is,
it's gonna be a bottled water lunch. I like how you slid that
in. It's pretty slick, buddy.
All right. All right. Let me know the rest of the
bad news. Well, so I
went past your place today, and probably gonna be like a week before everything
is done. No. Yes or no? No. Oh,
man. I've already told Omar I was gonna move out a couple of days ago.
Do you know when it's gonna be ready?
Should be ready by Wednesday, but that's all right. That's all right.
I got an idea. If it's too much problem with
you being here with Mr. Wright, I mean, I have a few extra rooms in
my place. You can always stay there. Really?
What? I can't do that. You're not holding up this process to make me
stay with you, right? I would never, ever do anything like that. Just checking,
but it does sound like a pretty good idea. No, really, sweetie. I just
want to. Just want to help you, that's all. Thank you.