Frankie, you're absolutely right. Marcy carried around
that raggedy stuffed elephant everywhere she went. Yeah.
Okay, so, mom, you got three points. Baby, you got one.
And I'm in the lead? Yes, sir. Okay, okay, okay. I got a question.
What is Marcy's least favorite food?
Ooh, I got it. I got this one.
You better go ahead and Yance. All right. Her least favorite
food is hot dogs. Cause she almost choked on one Fourth
of July holiday at Myra's house. Good job,
Adam. Good job. Sorry, Adam,
it was a marshmallow who almost did Marcie in.
Honey, I'm sure that Adam would know. I mean, he is her
fiance, right? Yeah, but I was there.
You were right. I saw. I completely forgot.
Okay, so here we go with the lightning round. Okay. Okay,
which does our Marcy Jewel prefer?
Basketball, soccer, or ping pong? Ping pong pong.
That was me. I said it first. Ping pong. I think it was a tie.
Yeah, sounded like it. Okay, George Jefferson.
Archie Bunker. Good one. Or Fred Sanford.
Definitely George Jefferson. And I'm moving on up.
That's why. You know how you say that? Okay, last one for me. High heels
or sneakers? Heels. Okay, I got one.
What if Marcy used to say she wanted to do when she grew up?
Oh, I know this one. How do I look?
Well, how do I look? Anyway,
thank you. I want to make the
world a better place and spread love and happiness wherever I go.
In heels, of course.
But the way we. I mean, I'm sorry. What do I win? What do I
win? What do I win? You win, Marcy.
Oh, I have a better idea.
How about a nice dinner for you
and yours? Congratulations, Blair. What?
Nice. From me and Mike.
Anybody want coffee?