I don't understand why Zordon won't just morph the Legend himself.
Why put them through all this crazy training? Technically, they wouldn't
be as strong as they are now. They learn how to work together and trust
one another. Yeah, that is kind of important.
Yeah, it is. Just like dodging skills.
Hey. No, man. I wasn't even looking.
What are y' all doing? Darling, I know you can't keep the door closed.
Yeah, I know. Mama Rose says time
for dinner. Leah, you staying? Please stay for dinner.
So can play pranks on my brother all night. And that cuz you would go
home. Nope. I'm staying. Yes.
Kids,
Y' all thought it was a game. Y' all thought it was a game,
all right.
Sure is. But this is for the bonfire tonight. Your all bowl from
earlier is in the microwave, sweetie.
I knew somebody was holding that little joker. Yeah. And that's game.
Ah, yes, it is. Yes, it is. Oh, hey, Donnie,
come on, get on these spades, bruh. Oh, no, I'm good, man. Y' all
can go on with your little spade game. I'm straight.
Still scared, I see. That's Donnie for you. Always playing
it safe. I ain't always playing it safe. I just
don't wanna play spades. I'm good, man. But spades is a tradition.
You know this. I don't know why you acting brand new.
Look, y' all already got four people already. I'm good. All right?
And Gene, I'm done. I am done. They beat me two times too many,
so I am finished. Yeah, you don't want to get. You get back. You don't
want to get back. No rematch your butt right here. And I'm pretty sure you
guys have a lot of catching up to do. Go ahead, take them out the
spot. Sit on down, Donnie. Get this
holiday beat down.