Just leave him alone. Let him be. Leave him alone.
I can't believe y'. All. I can't believe all y'. All. You set me up.
Nobody set you up, man. I told you
that he needed more time. Why did you listen to me?
I got excited.
Darius. I'm sorry, Mama Rose. I'm sorry.
Okay, Sorry. Y' all just got excited.
Feel like we ought to do this more often. I agree.
Yeah. Cool, cool. Get this
stuff out of here. So you. Do you mind?
Give me a second. Cool.
Don't throw those too much. You might hit an alligator.
Leah. Hey. Donnie.
What are you doing here? Well, this is kind of my home,
like. Like your. Your. Your house home?
My home. Oh. Oh, okay. All right. What are you doing
here, like, in the flesh? Well, I came back home to see my family
for Christmas. Wow. This must be a good Christmas. Yeah, it's been like,
8, 9 years old. Pushing 10,
and you still look the same. As well as you.
You ain't changing a bit either. Is that a compliment?
Um, so I see you about to buy you now.
Yeah. My aunt, she actually. She gave me your.
I don't know if you remember her. She traveled a lot when we were younger.
Yeah, I think I do. Yeah, she left her house to leave. Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm happy for you, but sad at the same time. It's okay.
It's been about three years, so I've had time to heal. Yeah, well,
I'm sorry for your loss. It's okay. She lived a great life.
Plus, I really needed the money. Things that got really bad
for me at one point, but things always work themselves out in the end,
you know? That's absolutely right. You're right.
Aaliyah, baby, come here.
Uh, I'll be right there.
All right. I guess I'll see you later then.
All right. Bye, Leah.
Bye.
Hey. What's that? Oh, it's just an old friend.
You ready to go? I can.