Yeah. How you like your clothes? They're nice. Man, they're stupid.
I didn't want these old clothes. I wanted toys. Well, maybe that's
all I could afford to get. You boys. You best be grateful for it.
You didn't have to sell that, you know. We ain't got no money. And I
didn't ask her you for. You think she did? You think she wanted to take
in two kids that ain't even hers?
Sir? Sir, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine. Okay. The bill, sir.
Thank you, chance. Thank you.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm fine. Okay.
Merry christmas. Yeah.
Just make it stop.
You know, the cure to a heavy heart is love. You get
yourself surrounded by a loving family and I promise you every
heartache will go away.