Sam,
it's time. So what you drinking, Donnie?
I'm not. Oh, come on, now. You got to get a beer or something.
Oh, man, I said I was going to come. I didn't say I was going
to drink, man. Just get a lime and a soda.
Yana used to get it when she came here during the pregnancy. L got.
All right, I have a crown.
You thinking it? I'm sorry.
Yeah, I have a Crown and Coke. Heavy on the crown,
light on the coke. Margarita with
no salt for me, please. Oh, man, that sounds good. Make it two of those
margaritas, right? You know,
I am really happy that you decided place
to have choice. I still ain't got my books, though.
But what's stopping you, man? You can have both the bookstore and
the agency if you really wanted to. I don't know.
See, that's your problem, bro. Always playing it safe.
I've been telling you that since we were kids. Life is
about taking risks. Well, you can't succeed if you're always afraid
to fail. I think it's very brave. Then he left and
went to a new area to start a new business from scratch. You know what?
And on that note, Aaliyah, let's have a toast, y'. All. What are we toasting
to? Let's toast to family and
friends and the. And the. And the joy that it brings.
Cheers. Cheers. Cheers. Cheers.
Hey, school, ain't that. Oh,
that's Leon.