Donnie. Donnie, are you
Where am I? Darius and Scooter, they bought you a home.
And I'm here because I'm your father and I
care about you. Don't say that, Donnie.
Is true. I'm tired of your lies.
Donnie, please try to stay calm.
What's going on? What's happening to him? It's okay. It's okay.
I'm sure he's going to be all right. He's going to be.
Hey, Donnie. She finally home?
What you doing here?
I gave you a piece of me.
What you do that for? Why would you ask a dumb question like
that? Because you're my son. And I love you. Donnie, if it wasn't
for your father, you wouldn't be here today. But you didn't tell me he was
the organ donor. And what difference would that have made.