Oh, August, we should probably talk.
Okay, well, talk. Look, I don't
want to mislead you anymore. No, I really think you're a nice guy,
but this whole pulling me in and getting close,
that's a little too soon. That's a bit much. So how much time do you
need me to give you? That's the thing. I don't know. I mean, my divorce
isn't even finalized.
Okay, well, take as long as you need.
Thank you. You know,
the first day you walked in my office, I wanted you.
August, I was married, and I totally respected
that. But now you're single and still
so. So fine.
I mean, you can't blame me for being the first guy putting my bed in.
I don't know what to say, though. Don't say nothing.
Tell you what. Let's just take it one day at a time. Can we
do that? Yes, please, let's. One day at a time. One day at a time.
Yeah. That's good. Let me ask you a question.
You still love Omar?
I do. I do. That's good,
because that tells me you're a good woman. But one
thing for sure, two things for certain. If you spend enough time with me,
I'm gonna break through all that. Oh, are you? I am.
I am. Okay, well, can you help me break through
these boxes for now? I can do that. Oh, I can do that. Thank you.
No, no, no, no. This can't be true.
Oh, gosh.
I can't believe this is happening.