Da, da, da, da, da, da, da okay, okay, ladies.
Ladies and gentlemen, I just want
to say welcome. Welcome to the Chandler
family holiday season kickoff. Are they simply
my favorite? Yes, but they are all out on the great Christmas tree hunt.
Dolphins. Now, as you know, we Chandler women.
What? We love Christmas.
We spend about six months talking about what we're gonna do for the holiday.
Right, Elizabeth? About what we should have done and who shouldn't
have gotten gifts. Marcie. Holy.
When are you gonna tell them? I have been blessed with such a special Christmas
gift. My beautiful daughter, Marcy has come home for
the first time in four years. We know Auntie Elizabeth.
And she has brought her handsome beau, Adam, with her.
Next thing we know, Adam will be putting a ring on it.
Oh, my goodness. Okay, that's a lot. That's a lot. No, no. Now, is it
that serious? I mean, could there be wedding bells? Okay, but we.
Marriage. I mean, honey, it's about time. At your age, I was already on my
second husband. I think Marcy would make a beautiful bride. So do I.
And a pretty decent mother, I might add. But not as good as my baby
girl, Dana. But decent. I tell you. Stephanie, I have to
be honest with you. At the rate Marcy was going, we thought you were never,
ever, ever gonna be a grandmother. Oh,
now, wouldn't that have been a hoot? That child's been planning on being a grandmama
ever since she became a mama. So, what say you, Adam? Are you gonna make
an honest woman out of Marcy? Okay. Or just keep living in sin?
Really? Oh, I think she's pretty honest.
So how long have you guys been dating? Got any kids? Man,
that's enough. Okay? Now, will this be your first marriage? You guys are
making him feel. Okay, okay, okay. Enough. Enough. We don't wanna run the man away.
Don't wanna scare him. Thank you. But, Marcy.
Could I be looking at my future son in law? Oh,
okay, now, that's just another sublimity. I need an answer from you.
I mean, are they gonna get married? All right, I'm done.
What do you mean, you're done? That's it? You got. Because, listen. Speak up,
boy. Are you gonna marry this woman or not? I wanna see my grandbabies
before I die. What do you mean you're. That's it? You got. Because, listen,
we just got here. Can we just plan? Don't you think
you should marry her? What is this? Credit score.
What's your credit score? I think it's a good idea.
I need an answer. Are you gonna marry this woman? Yes.
Oh. Cheers. Chairs.
Yes. I knew it. It was on the tip of his tongue.
So when? Spring,
next year. Spring? Yes.
And the colors? I think the color should be cream and crimson.
I don't know.