Yo. Hey, what's up, man? What's up, man? All right. No, yeah, I'm good.
Samara asked me to bring you a plate, man. We know you over here starving
to death, man. Make sure you tell her I said thanks. No doubt.
You know I had to put your wife out yesterday, right? Yeah, she told me
that they're only looking out for you guys, you know?
Yeah, but it's over between me and Carmen.
Yeah, I. I don't understand that.
Oh, I mean, you guys are meant for each other.
She's divorcing me, Jahad. Well, don't you understand? She just did that to
get some attention. Okay, now you sound like your wife. You don't give
someone divorce papers for attention. She's a woman. Do they ever
really need an excuse to do anything?
By the way, Carmen's pregnant.
I will dump that whole plate of food on your head. She's pregnant?
O, that's impossible. I'm sterile. And I've been that way for years.
What are you talking about? Oh, I guess those sperm counts have risen from the
dead, huh?
Carmen's. What?
Are you serious? Yeah.
Okay, if Carmen's pregnant, it's probably because she was messing around.
Oh, come on. Nah, man. She has been talking to this. This Boris Kojo
real estate looking cat. Really? Now you're talking crazy.
You know Carmen better than anyone, dawg. And she isn't out there
like that and you know it. No,
no, no, no. Maybe she's doing this to keep me from going to Europe.
Come on, dog, she loves you.
Besides, Samira and Jasmine were there with her when she took the test.
Four times, all positive.
We've been trying to have children for years,
but now we're going to the divorce courts. What does this all mean?
Job?
Wait a minute.