Mama Rose is dining. I thought you had moved to the big city.
Well, he did wait, but he just here visiting. Oh,
for how long? Oh, just for the holidays.
Well, maybe I'll see you around sometime. We gonna be at Mama
Roses, and we gonna be in the parade, so.
Okay. Maybe we will see each other. Yeah.
Yo, she was feeling you, dog. Why you ain't say
nothing? Sh.
Let me get into this sound.
So what's the abs, cuz? Any old friends get married or. Old friends?
Like who? You know, friends who you sign with. Ah.
So Matt got married to a man. What? Everybody went
crazy. And Thomas, Remember Tom? Yeah, Tom. So Tom
and his girl, they got married, moved to Hawaii, hit the lotto, and now
everybody thinking that they laundering money for the Creole mafia.
But, man, I got a feeling that ain't who you asking about.
Of course it is, man. I'm just trying to catch up. Yeah, catch up.
Nah, you trying to ask about Aaliyah.
That's exactly who it is, boy. You can't hide it. You wanna know about Aaliyah?
Okay. Come on.
Oh, man. Hey, nephew. What's down,
Mark? How you see you? Good to see you, man. How you doing, man?
It don't look like you've been eating much down in Atlanta. Oh, man, come on
now with that. What, you ain't got no labor to cook for you now,
Uncle Russ? You know Donald ain't got no woman taking care of him.
Nah, what don't look like happening is these floats look like they need some
work. That's what it look like need to happen. Gotta point that. And also,
come on, man. Ladies are more than just caregivers. Huh? Uh huh.
I guess that's a no, then. That's a no. Man. Just focus
on my work. That's all. Right. I guess some things never change,
do they? You know what, Darius?
What the hell going on out here anyway? Don't look, don't you two start.
Now, y' all ain't been together five minutes, and already y' all trying to get
it on and popping. Now what we need to do is go see Mama Rose
before she cut all us up. All right? Keeping on down your way,
you know, Y' all go ahead. I need to change and get out of these
work clothes. Yeah, you do. Hey, man,
I'm have to start calling you Hammer, man. You was about to get started,
man. You don't hurt him, Hammer.
Here goes the ham.
All you need is some pants. Come on,