You want to tell me what's going on,
Marcy? Leanne. Jewel. Chandler.
So I've been working with this big client,
supposed to turn my little boutique agency
into a major player in the advertiser world, you know, but when
Preston referred me to them, I had no idea
that they were embroiled in this lawsuit.
Well, maybe they weren't. Knowing Preston,
he probably saw the writing on the wall. But I had no idea. Oh,
had you known, would you have taken them on anyway?
Marcy, remember when you
asked me if there was a reason I hadn't been home?
Well, mom, there are several reasons.
You know, everybody in this family has had success.
Everybody. I have cousins who have all these fancy degrees
and successful husbands and
perfect children. Everyone except for me.
I was always the flighty one.
Wano had to find her wings, find her way.
And I found my way. I did.
I found my way. I finally
found something that I'm really good at. When I found it, I worked
really hard to make sure that I could get better.
I was gonna show him. That's all that mattered to me,
was being the best advertising executive that
I could be. So when this client
fell into my lap, I just knew. This was my break.
This was my chance. This was my opportunity to
prove to everybody that I could do it.
That I. I finally made it.
So to answer your question,
I don't know. I don't have an
answer for that. And it
scares me a little bit. You know what's scarier,
honey?
Deciding what to do now that you do know.