I'm ready to go. I see you now.
So see you.
Seriously?
Well on. It's getting late. Come on
time? We're gonna go to bed and give you a bath and we gonna watch
a mo.
So how about we keep this party going? We can hit up the bar,
have our first drink together.
I don't know. I don't know. I'm a little tired,
man. Come on, Donnie, man. Mama Rose is watching my kids tonight,
so I'm. I'm a free man. Come on, cuz, Scoot. I don't know,
man. Leah, you down
for an after party at the bar?
Why not? Who knows the next time I get to hang out with the Henson
brothers. That's what I'm talking about. My girl.
Hey, Ma. We'll be back,
okay? Y' all don't stay out too late. I expect all of you back up
here for Christmas Eve breakfast. Yes, ma'. Am. Yes, ma', am. We will. Mama Ron,
we have to bounce it.