So this is how you gonna do me? You just gonna give up on us?
You've given up on us a long time ago, Omar. Now you can have everything.
Even the house. I've already closed on another one and I'm moving out
What? You closed on a
house and you're moving out on Sunday? How long you been planning this?
Just think about it.
I really thought I knew you after all these years.
But right now, you just show me who you really are. This is not
about who I really am. This is about us. And a marriage that has been
tumbling for a long time.
Well, what if I don't sign him? Then I'm going to show you who I
really am. I'm gonna go after Wright's investments. So my suggestion
to you is just sign the papers. I want out.
So you're really leaving me?
You left me a long time ago, Oma.
Please, just sign the papers. I'm leaving with
Well, Sid, you might as well leave. Cause I ain't signing them things.
I'm not signing them,