We should talk. Yeah, Yeah, I want to talk to you also.
Yeah, you go first. Okay.
It's about this whole fake engagement thing. That's exactly what I wanted to talk to
you about. Okay. Something is going on with my
mother. She's really happy about this whole thing. I know, and I'm really sorry
that I put you on the spot like that, but your family, they really go
in. They were all over me and I had to say something. Tell me about
it. Tell me about it. Well. And you know my motto. Promise of anything,
work out the details. Work out the details later. I understand. And I know you
were trying to do your best, and I get it. Thank you.
But if you don't want to go through with this whole thing, I'll find another
way to break it to my mother. No, no, no, no. I want to.
You want to. I want to help you.
Yeah. I mean, that's why I'm here, right? To help you. You sure?
Yeah, for now. It's cool. Oh, God.
Okay. Okay. You have no idea how relieved I
am. Good. Well,
in that case,
you know what? For what? Here. Oh, I mean,
here. Marcy. Jewel, Will you
fake marry me? Yeah. Yes,
yes, yes, yes.
Um, since this is a fake engagement, I can
get you a fake ring. Oh, God. No mother can spot a fake from a
mile away. Here's what we'll do. We will go shopping for engagement rings. Real ones.
My treat. I'll just return it before we head back to
New York. All right, cool. All right, well, now that we're engaged, we should get
to know each other better. You know what? No, no. Our likes
and dislikes. Things that engaged people should know. Right, of course.
We'll just set aside a few minutes each night as we're working to go over
some personal details, all right? Personal details. Yeah. Cool.
Okay. All right, I'm gonna go to bed. All right.
I'm gonna get back to work. All right.
Okay. My room. Your room.
Good night.
Yeah. Okay. All right,