It. Hey, hey, hey, hey. Watch.
My bad. I'm sorry.
Do me a favor. Let me out. Let me out. Up here. I thought you
need to go to the airport. Yeah, yeah, I. I changed my mind. Let me
What are you doing here? Everybody's looking for you.
Leah. I'm just a big screw up. I can't get nothing right. Look,
no matter how screwed up things may seem, you can always get it right.
I wish that was true. It is.
Look, I could have went back to the house and been with Leon. But instead
I'm here looking for you. Along with your family.
Why would you do a thing like that? Because we love you.
And we want to be here for you.
Look, I can see the pain in your
eyes. It's the same thing that I felt when my
parents got divorced. You can't keep carrying that around.
Leah, I don't want to die. I don't want you to die either.
Lying. What should I do? I don't have
the answer to that question. But you do.
Right in here. What is it telling
Nothing. Listen,
I knew you was out here creeping. Come on,
Leon, just chill out, man. Let me explain it to you. Leon, stop.
You've been trying to ease your way back into our life ever since you got
here. Leon, stop. Thanks. Will you guys please just stop?
Oh, please stop.
Somebody help. Please.
Got it.
I'm okay. You okay?
Oh my God. Donnie. What?
He's not.
You can't have what don't belong to you. Sucker. What have you
done? I done?