You should receive that paperwork in about an hour.
Bravo. Thank you. Bravo. Yes. So you got the deal
closed. I don't know. Tell me, how'd you do it? I tell you.
But then I have to kill you.
No, really. You know what? All it needed was a little bit of a woman's
touch. That's it. I see. Mm. Oh, hey, before I forget,
Peter wanted me to ask you. Are you ready to move. Right. Investments. To Europe.
Oh, Europe again.
Okay, he already mentioned that,
but I turned it down because my wife and I wasn't ready to move to
Europe. I mean, it's so far away. And then. Not to mention, I still have
my North American client list. I mean, who's gonna take care of that? Hello?
I would. I can do it. You? Yes,
me. Come on. Then you and your wife can go off and have an amazing
life in Europe and live happily ever after.
I. I never even thought. I never thought
of it. But. But if it's you who's gonna take over the client list,
I actually really might consider Europe. Yeah? Yeah. But I'd be going by myself.
What? Wait. Why? I'm getting
a divorce. Omar. Oh,
my gosh. Yeah. I'm so. I am so sorry.
As of when, though? As of.
It just kind of came out of nowhere. Oh,
gosh. Do you want to talk about it?
No. Nah, it's cool. I mean, it's my cross
to bear, so, I mean, if you. Whatever. But going
back to Pete. Let's set that up. Yeah. Get that going.
Cause I think. I mean, Europe sounds nice right now. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Done.
Wow. I am so scared of marriage.
Why not? Well, if you're scared of marriage,
why are you saying that? Cause you haven't found the right guy. Uh, thanks.
Don't remind me. What are you talking about, Kareem?
You probably got tons of guys knocking your door down. Negative. You know
why? Because guys find successful, independent women,
they're intimidated by us. Not me.
I think it's sexy. No, seriously.
In fact, I think it's your best feature. So you're saying
I'm ugly? No. Hell, no. I think you super bad.
But, you know, I'm married, so I'm not even gonna go there.
I thought you said you were getting a divorce.