Man, I know what you were trying to do, Adam, and I
really. I do appreciate it, but, you know,
it's. Oh, hey, look at this. Look, Look. That's what
I'm talking about. Nice. Mm.
You know, we can just play it off for now. I mean, we're only gonna
be here a few days. We'll be in New York. We're gonna have a nasty
breakup, huh? Problem solved.
I mean, till next Christmas, right? I mean, I guess,
but I. Hey, Mom. Hi, honey. Hi, Adam.
Hey, I'm gonna let you two have your time,
okay? Okay. See you soon. Okay. Okay.
All right. Good night.
I like him. Yeah, He's a good guy, Ma. He's nice.
You know, being out here brings back such memories.
I remember when you used to run out here as a little girl,
sit in that very rocking chair when you thought your little world was coming to
an end. Yeah. And you come right on out after me and say,
get your butt back in the house, missy, and do your homework, or it's gonna
end a lot sooner than you think. Stop exagger,
Marcy. Did you bring work with you? No. No. Come on.
Heavens no, Mom. Who brings work to Christmas? I'm looking at wedding
invitations. Well, let me see. Honey. Honey, we got a year.
You're right. It's so exciting, honey.
You know, it would have been nice if Adam could have gone with the guys.
He needs to get to know his future in laws, you know? Yeah. About Adam.
Mom. Guess. Mom, are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm okay. What is going on? What is this? Band aid?
Routine blood work. I'm fine. I want to talk about you and.
Never mind me. I want to talk about you and Adam.
I am so proud of you, baby. Oh, my God.
And how you took your time, how you built
your business. Sweetheart. You waited for the
right man to come into your life. I know
I've been pushy at times, but I want the best for you. I love you.
And I want you to experience that love and joy that
I shared with your father, God rest his soul.
You know what?
Your happiness is all the medicine Mother needs.
I love you. Come here. Come here,
pumpkin. Love you.