You. You want to
go ahead and get that?
Uh, you know what? Let me just check.
But no, babe, I, I. I just want you to know that I'm. I'm.
I'm. I'm. I'm listening to you, and you.
You are right. And damn.
And I hear everything that you're saying, so that's why I'm
saying, like, you know, I mean, you have any other suggestions? What do you think
about Mars? Mm.
I've always wanted to go there. I mean, I could probably call my travel agent.
Omar, give me your phone.
What? Wait, what are you talking about? He's handing your phone.
Please give me your phone. I would gladly give you my phone, but I
don't bring my phone to dinner, nor do I sleep with my phone or shower
with my phone. I mean, is there something you're hiding?
How dare you accuse. No, no, no, no. I'm not hiding anything.
Okay, then, fine. Give me your phone. No.
Okay, then can you please put
your phone away? Because this is supposed to be my time.
Remember that little promise you made me today? My time phone
stays where it is.
Now, what about that vacation?