There he is. He's arrived.
Good to see you, man. Old Donny in
the building. Here we go with this, man. Listen, they don't call me Donnie anymore.
My name is Domo. Hey, man. Come on, man. You gonna always be Cousin Donnie
to me. Oh. How you feeling, man? You looking good. Appreciate it. Look like you
done shrunk a little bit. I remember. I. I think I remember you being
a little bit tall.
You ain't tell nobody I was coming, did you? Nah, you told me not to.
Remember? Yeah, I was just making sure you remember.
Why you patting your foot like that, man? You nervous or something?
Yeah, I just ain't been here in a minute. Oh. Oh, I know, man.
You missed the birth of both of my kids. Both? Yes. You got
kids? Man, listen, My son is 4 years old, and my baby girl just
turned 1. Hey, you remember Yana, right? Yana. Yana. Yana.
You talking about Lil Yana? Hey, man,
she ain't Lil Yana no more. What?
Yeah, man, that's my baby mama. You sound crazy
calling her your baby mama, man. Come on, man. Man, listen.
Everybody. Everybody ain't trying to get married, man. Me and her, we. We good.
Just what we are. I mean, but come on, man. You gotta put some respect
on her name just a little bit, man. You call her your spouse or your
woman, you can't call her your baby mama. Cause, look at me. Do I look
like the person that's walking around here using words like spouse? No, you don't.
No. But,
man, I gotta tell you, man, on a serious note, man,
I miss you, man. We miss you. Things just
been different since you left. Different? Man,
it's funny. Everything seemed the same.
See, I'm not talking about location. I'm talking
about the vibes. You know, like, you know, that type of stuff. I mean,
hell, it just. It just ain't been the same since you left.
Wait. Hey, man, ain't Mama Rose house back this way, boy. Where you going?
Yeah. Yeah, but you know you can't come back here. You can't come back
home, man, without getting the po. Boy. Oh, my God. We going to go.
We about to go get a po. Boy. Got to.
Come on. Let's go. Man, you know how long it's been since I had a.
Too long, Too long, too long. Come on, man. Let's go. I'm. Man, I'm so
hungry. Glad you said.