Me?
Shade in all her glory.
And how long have you been standing there?
Well, long enough to fantasize how to get a husband like you.
How sweet. Anyway, um, I gotta go. Uh, take care of your sister, right? If she gives you any trouble, just call me.
Okay. Wow. All right.
Oh, jealous much?
Shadi, come here. Oh, smallie, how are you? Oh, so sorry. When did you come in? Um, early this morning. How do you say not to disturb you?
It was just snoozing.
I know, man, that stupid anxiety tab. Why do you still take them?
I don't have a choice.
Hmm, jollof rice, chicken, fruits. Where did you meet this amazing man again?
I was raped and shot, and he was a doctor on duty.
Are you really sure you want to go down that road? I didn't think so either.
Cheers to me, Jo.
What have you been up to, girl?
The usual, you know. I have plenty gist for you. You did what? Broke up with him?
Why so alarmed? Because this is the third guy this year, dummy.
Yeah, but sis, you know me, a broken relationship is better than a broken marriage. That line again?
Yes, that line again. But you know me, I won't settle for less.
What's his crime? Sex.
The guy wants to have sex in the morning, in the afternoon, all the time. I may be everything, but a dog is not on the list. Now, I thought that's what this generation is all about. Sex, sex, sex. They can't get enough of sex. My sentiments exactly. Well, let's talk about you. I mean, you've been having sex for over 4 years now. What has it done for you?