Turn around and look at me,
young man. No, turn around and
look at me, young man. Now
listen to me, son. I know Nate
and you are very close, very
close, and I'm not trying to
separate you two from each
other, but that crazy mother of
yours back there, I don't I
don't care if we never seen her
another day in our life. Because
see, son, you at the age right
now where the decisions that you
make today will affect your
entire future. I don't know what
you want to be in life, but as
my son, I only want the best for
you. I want you to be that kid
that came from this hood and
made something out of himself.
Yes, Dad, I know. I think I want
to be a fireman or a cop.
You kidding me, right?
What's wrong with that?
Ain't nothing at all wrong with
that, but if you do it, do it
right. You understand? And above
all, remember one thing. I'm
your dad and I love you.
I love you too, Dad.
That's what I'm talking about.
What's up, little man?
What's up, Dre? Oh, you know me?
Yeah, I seen you around. I see
you do your thing. So you know
what it is that I do? Yeah, get
money. Mind if I sit down?
Whatever, it's a free country.
Listen, man, I'm gonna be
straight up with you. I've been
watching you. I've been watching
you a while now. I like the way
you move, the way you handle
yourself. Like that bullshit
that happened over here? Niggas.
Always trying to be gangsters,
but they ain't gonna do shit.
But see, that don't bother you,
huh? You got hard, liked it.
Okay, so what you saying? I'm
trying to put you down, nigga.
Put some bread in your pocket. I
mean, if you ain't scared.
Nigga, I'm hungry. I ain't
scared of nothing. Listen, I'mma
sleep on it. Stay real. All
right, cool. Oh yeah, what they
call you? Big Nate.
Big Nate.
I like that.
Stay up, nigga. Yeah, all right.