You two motherfuckers must hate
my ass.
You know what?
I should have left your ass in
jail because you ain't no good
to me here. Now get the fuck out
of my car. That's what the
problem is. I'm out here—
You're following me on my
probation? Oh, hell no.
Oh, shut up, Rob. Go and talk to
them boys, Rob.
I'm not talking to them.
Ain't my turn. Them your damn
turn.
Rob, come on, man.
You need to help me. Stop
ignoring me.
Hey, man.
Man, I told you I'm straight.
Man, calm down. I just wanted to
say thanks for having my back
today at the park, man.
Man, you was getting the shit
beat out of you before I rushed
that big-ass nigga.
Man, I had a grip on that fool.
Just when you came over, he
flipped me over. Don't get it
twisted, bro, I ain't need no
help.
Nah, whatever you say. But on
the real, you know I got your
back no matter what.
For sure, man.
Destiny! Destiny! Who let that
goddamn dog out?
What, nigga?
So you couldn't call, right? You
couldn't call. Now see, that's
exactly what I'm talking about.
You called me.
Hey, Mark.
Hey, Marcus.
What, man? What happened?
Man, I think your daddy outside,
man.
Nigga, let me tell you.
Hold up, hold up.
You couldn't call to tell me
that Marcus got arrested today?
Huh, Destiny? You know what,
Destiny? I didn't even come
right here to argue with you.
You did.
All I came right here for is my
son. You what? I should have
been did this a long time ago.
But after today, that was the
last straw. That was the last
straw.
He ain't going nowhere.
Oh, yeah? Marcus, go pack your
things. You coming to stay with
me. What?
Boy, don't you move. Don't you
move.
Young man, go and get your
things now.
Ron?
Damn, man, guys, this some
bullshit, man.
You know Mama don't like me,
man. What you think gonna happen
to me if you leave?
Man, you gonna be straight.
This shit fucked up, man. What
I'm supposed to do now, man?
Huh?
What the fuck I'mma do?
Nate, listen, man. It ain't even
like that. Ain't nothing gonna
change with me or without me.
Watch what I tell you.
Whatever, man.
Damn, bro, what you going to
leave a nigga hanging?
That's right, you motherfucker.
Put that on my life.
This is bullshit, man.
Stay up, bro.
Hold up, man.
It smells fine. Fuck you,
motherfucker. This is my house.
Doing all that crazy crap up in
here.
You want him to be like you, an
uncle?
Let's hurry up. Let's go. I
should have been got you from
around here a long time ago.
Well, what you standing there
looking stupid for?
You know what?
I'm tired of y'all always put me
down, talk about this going to
school shit. Man, look around
this, man. We still in the
ghetto. The fridge on E, and you
stay broke. So? So what? I guess
you want me to grow up to be
like you, huh? No thanks. I'mma
be like Dre.
Aw, shit.
He got money, respect, fresh
cars and all that. What we got?
You and Rob both ain't got a pot
to piss in.
Oh yeah? You gonna end up just
like your daddy.
Dead.
Man, you know what? I'mma show
y'all.
You show me.
Yeah, I'mma show y'all.
You gonna show me? Yeah.
Yeah. Shit.
Fuck that.
And you not my daddy either,
Rod.
Loser.