I've been waiting for this deer
a long time.
I haven't seen Marcus in almost
a decade. The only real blood
family I ever had in my life. He
never did respect the hustlers
in the hood. And came to this.
Yo, what the fuck you gotta say
to me? Bruh, I know shit was
hard for you. You don't know
nothing about my life. Talking
about shit was hard for me.
Nigga, I ain't seen you since I
was 14. How the fuck you gonna
tell me how hard life been for
me? Bruh, I was right there with
you.
Let me take you back to the
beginning. Or rather, the end.
What?
Nothing but nets, nigga. Swiss.
Okay, where my money at?
What the fuck you said, nigga?
Tell y'all little niggas coming
out here this time the real way.
What you going to do with that?
This nigga need to get his ass
Nigga, get off my brother. Fuck
nigga, get off my brother. All
right, come on, come on. Damn,
what the fuck you gonna do with
that?
Marcus tried hard to keep us out
of trouble. But being my
brother, it was easier said than
done.
Nigga, say something now, man.
Nah, fuck that, man.
Drop the fucking knife! Put it
down now, man! Let me go, man.
Shut the fuck up and keep
walking.
So you saying you tripped and
fell over the knife, right? So
how'd the knife get in your
hands?
Man, why you keep asking me the
same question?
Just answer the goddamn
questions.
I don't remember, man.
You don't remember what? How he
got stabbed or how the knife got
in your hands?
He came at me with the knife
first, man.
And then what?
Shit, you got the notepad, you
tell me.
What? Okay, smartass. Look, I
know you think you're a little
badass, but when that wagon come
to take you down to juvie, we're
gonna see just how bad your ass
really is. You're gonna learn.
All right, Gray, what we got?
I made that call over to Jackson
and they said that the jit gonna
make it.
Good.
But they gonna be discharging
him in a couple of hours, so
before he get out, you want me
to send Jones over there to take
a statement from him?
Nah, let's deal with that in the
morning. Where's his brother?
Well, Marcy's bringing him down
from interrogation room 4.
Here they come, boy.
What's up, Gray? Brooks.
Remember what I told you, stay
out of trouble.
Little man, step inside here
with your brother. And
gentlemen, we'll be with you in
a few minutes.
Damn, dog.
Have a seat, thank you.
You ain't say shit, did you?
Nah.
Good. You don't say nothing, we
straight.
What the fuck we gonna do with
these two clowns? Everybody
saying they ain't seen shit
nowhere.
Hmm. I don't give a shit, man.
Send them home.
Fuck.