You could be nothing and become something. You know what I'm saying? He went and
seen Scarface and left the movie theater and went and bought a great Porsche.
He did his as a movie, I did mine as facts.
I got it just like he got. I got suitcases, bags of money.
I got motherfuckers flying two and three keys of coke from this
coast to that coast to this coast. I done own that. You can sum up
Scarface in two words. Bang, bang, snort, snort. Bang, bang is for gunfire. Snort,
snort is for cocaine. There's a lot of both in Scarface. And ain't just
talking about it. Ask them white folks. It's documented who I was.
I built a million dollar house. I had Rolls Royces, every car you can
order. The world know who I am. I'm here today telling this story, man.
Telling this Tal.