Oh, for me?
I didn't mean it like that. I mean.
What I was trying to say is. It's okay. Sex is not everything.
Just finish the dishes. Just finish dishes.
Okay? I mean,
people shouldn't. Should. Should.
Gosh.
Please. Please. I don't have a roommate.
Should I. You go to st. Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Okay. Yes,
sir. Come on.
Come on. Your clothes.
Wait, wait. Let me show you. Let me show you. Let me show you.
Let me show you. Let me show you. Let me show you.
Please. Open your eyes, miss. For me. You can do this.
Can you hear me, Fumi? You can do this.
I knew you could do it.
Sis. For me.
Are you okay?
Is everything okay?
Please talk to me now,
Sis.
Okay? Please. Can you at least make a sound so I know you're
fine? Please. Now,
sis. You know what?
That's it. I'm calling your husband.